Sentence,Word,Named Entity
1,https://t.co/CzfTXhfWQ9,O
1,Watch,O
1,live,O
1,online,O
1,now,O
1,|,O
1,Faur\xc3\xa9,O
1,Requiem,O
1,-,O
1,Dedicated,O
1,to,O
1,the,O
1,memory,O
1,of,O
1,Her,B-PER
1,Majesty,I-PER
1,#QueenElizabethII,I-PER
1,Surprisingly,O
1,moving,O
1,.,O
2,She,O
2,lived,O
2,a,O
2,life,O
2,of,O
2,dignity,O
2,and,O
2,honor,O
2,",",O
2,whatever,O
2,you,O
2,think,O
2,of,O
2,empire,O
2,and,O
2,colonialism,O
2,.,O
2,#history,O
2,#continuity,O
3,Today,O
3,",",O
3,Leon,B-PER
3,",",I-PER
3,Activities,I-PER
3,Coordinator,I-PER
3,&amp,O
3,;,O
3,Kelly,B-PER
3,",",I-PER
3,General,I-PER
3,Manager,I-PER
3,at,O
3,Northampton,B-LOC
3,House,I-LOC
3,",",O
3,paid,O
3,their,O
3,respects,O
3,to,O
3,HM,B-PER
3,Queen,I-PER
3,Elizabeth,I-PER
3,II,I-PER
3,&amp,O
3,;,O
3,left,O
3,flowers,O
3,&amp,O
3,;,O
3,a,O
3,signed,O
3,letter,O
3,from,O
3,the,B-PER
3,residents,I-PER
3,&amp,O
3,;,O
3,staff,B-PER
3,.,O
4,A,O
4,historical,O
4,moment,O
4,in,O
4,time,O
4,",",O
4,never,O
4,to,O
4,be,O
4,forgotten,O
4,",",O
4,forever,O
4,in,O
4,our,O
4,hearts,O
4,#history,O
4,#ncctuk,O
4,https://t.co/QM6uKBT7xg,O
5,I,O
5,had,O
5,an,O
5,incredible,O
5,time,O
5,visiting,O
5,the,O
5,open,O
5,house,O
5,at,O
5,the,O
5,TTC's,B-LOC
5,Harvey,I-LOC
5,Shop,I-LOC
5,&amp,O
5,;,O
5,Streetcar,B-LOC
5,Way,I-LOC
5,today,O
5,.,O
6,All,O
6,the,O
6,volunteers,B-PER
6,&amp,I-PER
6,;,I-PER
6,visitors,I-PER
6,who,I-PER
6,chatted,I-PER
6,with,I-PER
6,me,I-PER
6,made,O
6,it,O
6,an,O
6,extra,O
6,special,O
6,day,O
6,.,O
7,Thank,O
7,you,O
7,all,O
7,!,O
7,#ttc,O
7,#unitedway,B-ORG
7,#charity,O
7,#transit,O
7,#history,O
7,#ttcxunitedway,B-ORG
7,#hopkindesign,O
7,#ttcpics,O
7,https://t.co/mb4cJyLQLI,O
8,The,O
8,front,B-FAC
8,porch,I-FAC
8,of,I-FAC
8,a,I-FAC
8,rooming,I-FAC
8,house,I-FAC
8,in,O
8,Portsmouth,B-GPE
8,",",I-GPE
8,Virginia,I-GPE
8,",",I-GPE
8,United,I-GPE
8,States,I-GPE
8,",",O
8,photographed,O
8,by,O
8,John,B-PER
8,Vachon,I-PER
8,in,O
8,March,O
8,1941,O
8,.,O
9,Credit:,O
9,@/sebcolorisation,B-PER
9,on,O
9,Instagram,B-ORG
9,https://t.co/KfEjyDTQjX,O
9,#history,O
9,#usa,B-GPE
9,#unitedstates,B-GPE
9,https://t.co/rouxAxe4BK,O
10,https://t.co/QZ8YEl68qS,O
10,Interested,O
10,in,O
10,Hockey,O
10,and,O
10,How,O
10,It,O
10,All,O
10,Started,O
10,?,O
11,We're,O
11,your,O
11,place,O
11,.,O
12,Not,O
12,interested,O
12,?,O
13,Not,O
13,to,O
13,worry,O
13,we're,O
13,just,O
13,getting,O
13,started,O
13,on,O
13,new,O
13,topics,O
13,and,O
13,new,O
13,stories,O
13,.,O
14,Come,O
14,check,O
14,us,O
14,out,O
14,and,O
14,join,O
14,the,B-ORG
14,community,I-ORG
14,\xf0\x9f\x98\x81,O
14,#HockeyTwitter,O
14,#History,O
14,#ShamelessSelfPromoSaturday,O
14,#blog,O
15,@HertzCompresor,B-PER
15,is,O
15,amazing,O
15,!,O
16,With,O
16,multiple,O
16,tanks,O
16,set,O
16,up,O
16,throughout,O
16,the,B-FAC
16,shop,I-FAC
16,",",O
16,we,O
16,use,O
16,them,O
16,every,O
16,day,O
16,to,O
16,make,O
16,our,O
16,projects,O
16,run,O
16,smoothly,O
16,!,O
16,#countskustoms,O
16,#countingcars,O
16,#lasvegas,B-GPE
16,#history,O
16,#hertz,O
16,https://t.co/aPwucn4sh8,O
17,@BBCWorld,B-ORG
17,Northern,B-GPE
17,Ireland,I-GPE
17,is,O
17,on,O
17,a,O
17,sticky,O
17,wicket,O
17,post,O
17,Brexit,O
17,#History,O
17,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
17,https://t.co/0BHFOONrjJ,O
18,The,O
18,Bay,B-LOC
18,Of,I-LOC
18,Pigs,I-LOC
18,Invasion,O
18,#history,O
18,#shorts,O
18,https://t.co/YTKMbXa5MJ,O
18,via,O
18,@YouTube,B-ORG
19,Per,O
19,@AKurmanaev,B-PER
19,@nytimesworld,B-ORG
19,piece,O
19,",",O
19,Caribbean,B-PER
19,leaders,I-PER
19,are,O
19,calling,O
19,#Haiti,B-GPE
19,a,O
19,failed,O
19,state,O
19,and,O
19,the,O
19,crisis,O
19,there,O
19,a,O
19,low-intensity,O
19,civil,O
19,war,O
19,Eminent,O
19,#Hatian,O
19,#historian,O
19,",",O
19,Dr.,B-PER
19,Fatton,I-PER
19,",",O
19,explained,O
19,Haiti\'s,B-GPE
19,#History,O
19,in,O
19,this,O
19,podcast:,O
19,https://t.co/WjqAl6or1X,O
19,https://t.co/8bXnxBoYvs,O
20,contact,O
20,us,O
20,for:-,O
20,#Online,O
20,classes,O
20,#Presentations,O
20,#Essay,O
20,due,O
20,#Research,O
20,#Javascript,O
20,#Case,O
20,study,O
20,#Python,O
20,#Homework,O
20,#Biology,O
20,#History,O
20,#Calculus,O
20,#Economics,O
20,#Econometrics,O
20,#Maths,O
20,#Chemistry,O
20,#Assignments,O
20,#Programming,O
20,evephiliph20@gmail.com,O
20,+1(360),O
20,548-6038,O
20,DM,O
20,@prof_cecil,B-PER
21,as,O
21,caption,O
21,1924-1944,O
21,By,O
21,Unknown,O
21,#\xe4\xb8\xad\xe5\x9b\xbd\xe5\x8e\x86\xe5\x8f\xb2,O
21,#History,O
21,#photograph,O
21,https://t.co/gq3MJN61p9,O
22,\xf0\x9f\x91\x89,O
22,\xf0\x9f\x91\x88,O
22,The,O
22,History,O
22,of,O
22,Whoo,O
22,Cheongidan,O
22,Hwahyun,O
22,Cream,O
22,Premium,O
22,Radiant,O
22,Regenerating,O
22,Cream,O
22,Longlasting,O
22,@buy1_best,B-PER
22,#The,O
22,#History,O
22,#of,O
22,#Whoo,O
22,#Cheongidan,O
22,#Hwahyun,O
22,#Cream,O
22,#Premium,O
22,#fashion,O
22,#lifestyle,O
22,Are,O
22,you,O
22,ready,O
22,to,O
22,be,O
22,#pretty,O
22,?,O
22,!,O
22,https://t.co/21d6N6lJLp,O
23,#Armenia's,B-GPE
23,entire,O
23,history,O
23,is,O
23,one,O
23,of,O
23,atrocities,O
23,against,O
23,other,O
23,nations,O
23,.,O
24,And,O
24,all,O
24,Armenian,B-ORG
24,terrorist,I-ORG
24,organizations,I-ORG
24,such,O
24,as,O
24,Dashnaktsutyun,B-ORG
24,and,O
24,ASALA,B-ORG
24,are,O
24,recognized,O
24,as,O
24,terrorist,O
24,by,O
24,the,O
24,#CIA,B-ORG
24,.,O
24,Armenia,B-GPE
24,must,O
24,pull,O
24,itself,O
24,together,O
24,and,O
24,apologize,O
24,for,O
24,its,O
24,#history,O
24,and,O
24,the,O
24,lies,O
24,it,O
24,promotes,O
24,.,O
25,Hire,O
25,our,O
25,legit,O
25,services,O
25,in,O
25,;,O
25,#Math,O
25,#Chem,O
25,.,O
26,#Essay,O
26,due,O
26,.,O
27,#Paper,O
27,write,O
27,#English,O
27,#Paper,O
27,pay,O
27,.,O
28,#Someone,O
28,help,O
28,paper,O
28,#Case,O
28,study,O
28,#essaypay,O
28,#Online,O
28,class,O
28,#Religion,O
28,#book,O
28,review,O
28,#Assignment,O
28,#Chemistry,O
28,#History,O
28,Kindly,O
28,dm,O
28,us,O
28,rn,O
28,@superb_writings,B-ORG
29,Photo,O
29,By,O
29,ArtTower,B-PER
29,|,I-PER
29,Pixabay,I-PER
29,#vintagecar,O
29,#classicautomobile,O
29,#style,O
29,#americanhistory,O
29,#history,O
29,#sketching,O
29,#cartechnology,O
29,#cardesign,O
29,https://t.co/jUZS9TzpoE,O
30,#FalseFlag=#FalseProphets,O
30,NO,O
30,#God,O
30,NO,O
30,#humans,O
30,#colonized,O
30,#white\xc3\x97#POC,O
30,#AlienSINwonderLAND,O
30,#SlaveTrade,O
30,NO,O
30,#Heritage'#History,O
30,#honorThy,O
30,#FATHER'#Name*#Land,O
30,OUR,O
30,#Mothers'#PRIDE,O
30,Our,O
30,#Fathers'#MadeForYOUAndME,O
30,In,O
30,#God's,O
30,#NAME,O
30,#FREE,O
30,For,O
30,Thy,O
30,#SAKE,O
30,O'#USA&amp,B-GPE
30,;'#HumanRace,B-ORG
30,https://t.co/baxlXdYwd5,O
31,Kindly,O
31,dm,O
31,if,O
31,you,O
31,need,O
31,help,O
31,.,O
31,#assignments,O
31,#Essaydue,O
31,#Essays,O
31,#philosophy,O
31,#Psychology,O
31,#homework,O
31,#ethics,O
31,#history,O
31,#English,O
31,#essaypay,O
31,#presentations,O
31,#dissertation,O
31,#essaypay,O
31,#Powerpoint,O
31,College,O
31,course,O
31,@writershub027,B-PER
32,Every,O
32,Australian,B-LOC
32,town,I-LOC
32,has,O
32,incredible,O
32,royal,O
32,history,O
32,.,O
33,Here's,O
33,the,O
33,story,O
33,of,O
33,just,O
33,one,B-LOC
33,of,I-LOC
33,those,I-LOC
33,towns,I-LOC
33,.,O
33,#royalvisits,O
33,#metaldetecting,O
33,#history,O
33,#historyoutthere,O
33,https://t.co/gcSCfUricO,O
34,Big,O
34,tweet,O
34,out,O
34,to,O
34,my,B-PER
34,sister,I-PER
34,who,I-PER
34,queued,I-PER
34,and,I-PER
34,lived,I-PER
34,a,I-PER
34,part,I-PER
34,in,I-PER
34,history,I-PER
34,.,O
35,Very,O
35,proud,O
35,of,O
35,you,O
35,Karen,B-PER
35,\xf0\x9f\x91\x8f,O
35,#QueenelizabethII,B-PER
35,#history,O
35,#family,O
35,https://t.co/5D29khNdMV,O
36,PAY,O
36,US,O
36,TO,O
36,HELP,O
36,IN,O
36,YOUR,O
36,DUE,O
36,Homework,O
36,Assignments,O
36,Essay,O
36,Exams,O
36,Online,O
36,classes,O
36,WhatsApp,O
36,+1(551)292-7202,O
36,https://t.co/MmQQtVS7o6,O
36,DISCORD,O
36,SERVER,O
36,https://t.co/2Dkrufn2kB,O
36,#Chemistry,O
36,#Physics,O
36,#Geography,O
36,#Biology,O
36,#Maths,O
36,#English,O
36,#History,O
36,#USA,B-GPE
36,#UAE,B-GPE
36,#Canada,B-GPE
36,#UK,B-GPE
36,#Australia,B-GPE
36,#Kuwait,B-GPE
37,PAY,O
37,US,O
37,TO,O
37,HELP,O
37,IN,O
37,YOUR,O
37,DUE,O
37,Homework,O
37,Assignments,O
37,Essay,O
37,Exams,O
37,Online,O
37,classes,O
37,WhatsApp,O
37,+1(551)292-7202,O
37,https://t.co/MmQQtVS7o6,O
37,DISCORD,O
37,SERVER,O
37,https://t.co/2Dkrufn2kB,O
37,#History,O
37,#Sociology,O
37,#Philosophy,O
37,#Psychology,O
37,#Astronomy,O
37,#Geology,O
37,#law,O
37,#USA,B-GPE
37,#UAE,B-GPE
37,#Canada,B-GPE
37,#UK,B-GPE
37,#Australia,B-GPE
37,#Kuwait,B-GPE
38,Kindly,O
38,dm,O
38,if,O
38,you,O
38,need,O
38,help,O
38,.,O
38,#assignments,O
38,#Essaydue,O
38,#Essays,O
38,#philosophy,O
38,#Psychology,O
38,#homework,O
38,#ethics,O
38,#history,O
38,#English,O
38,#essaypay,O
38,#presentations,O
38,#dissertation,O
38,#essaypay,O
38,#Powerpoint,O
38,College,O
38,course,O
38,@graciepapers,B-PER
39,Kindly,O
39,dm,O
39,if,O
39,you,O
39,need,O
39,help,O
39,.,O
39,#assignments,O
39,#Essaydue,O
39,#Essays,O
39,#philosophy,O
39,#Psychology,O
39,#homework,O
39,#ethics,O
39,#history,O
39,#English,O
39,#essaypay,O
39,#presentations,O
39,#dissertation,O
39,#essaypay,O
39,#Powerpoint,O
39,College,O
39,course,O
40,@domsarz,B-PER
40,@MrMattSavage,B-PER
40,The,O
40,history,O
40,of,O
40,white,B-PER
40,people,I-PER
40,as,O
40,colonists,B-PER
40,",",O
40,slave,B-PER
40,owners,I-PER
40,",",O
40,leading,O
40,lynch,O
40,mobs,O
40,",",O
40,championing,O
40,Jim,B-PER
40,Crow,I-PER
40,and,O
40,developing,O
40,systems,O
40,of,O
40,institutionalized,O
40,racism,O
40,are,O
40,all,O
40,facts,O
40,in,O
40,evidence,O
40,.,O
41,Not,O
41,claiming,O
41,or,O
41,denying,O
41,your,O
41,history,O
41,doesn\xe2\x80\x99t,O
41,make,O
41,it,O
41,go,O
41,away,O
41,.,O
41,#criticalracetheory,O
41,is,O
41,#history,O
41,.,O
42,Pretty,O
42,interesting,O
42,interview,O
42,by,O
42,@NickCannon,B-PER
42,and,O
42,@IAmKRSOne,B-PER
42,.,O
42,#NickCannon,B-PER
42,#interview,O
42,#History,O
42,#krsone,B-PER
42,#share,O
42,#RETWEEET,O
42,#SaturdayNight,O
42,#godisgood,O
42,https://t.co/TTnBmVkZpG,O
43,I've,O
43,noticed,O
43,a,O
43,very,O
43,large,O
43,amount,O
43,of,O
43,traffic,O
43,visiting,O
43,my,O
43,site,O
43,via,O
43,Bing,B-ORG
43,search,O
43,",",O
43,compared,O
43,to,O
43,Google,B-ORG
43,.,O
44,Anyone,B-PER
44,who,I-PER
44,owns,I-PER
44,a,I-PER
44,website,I-PER
44,or,I-PER
44,blog,I-PER
44,",",O
44,a,O
44,good,O
44,tip,O
44,is,O
44,to,O
44,upload,O
44,your,O
44,sitemap,O
44,and,O
44,SEO,O
44,settings,O
44,to,O
44,Bing,B-ORG
44,search,O
44,engine,O
44,.,O
44,#DailyTips,O
44,#Bing,B-ORG
44,#Google,B-ORG
44,#History,O
44,#Website,O
44,#Bloggers,O
44,#NotAnAd,O
45,Louis,B-PER
45,the,I-PER
45,Great\'s,I-PER
45,daughter,I-PER
45,Mary,I-PER
45,was,O
45,crowned,O
45,King,B-PER
45,of,I-PER
45,#Hungary,I-PER
45,OTD,O
45,in,O
45,1382,O
45,https://t.co/aZcYiqKvTm,O
45,#travel,O
45,#history,O
46,Kindly,O
46,hmu,O
46,for,O
46,quality,O
46,grades,O
46,.,O
46,#essay,O
46,#homework,O
46,#assignment,O
46,#hw,O
46,#math,O
46,#chem,O
46,#biology,O
46,#onlineclass,O
46,#English,O
46,#mymathlab,O
46,#nursing,O
46,#labreport,O
46,#economics,O
46,#history,O
46,#sociology,O
46,#psychology,O
46,#dissertations,O
46,Dm,O
46,https://t.co/KxSMPy4Btk,O
47,Hire,O
47,our,O
47,legit,O
47,services,O
47,in,O
47,;,O
47,#Math,O
47,#Chem,O
47,.,O
48,#Essay,O
48,due,O
48,#Paper,O
48,write,O
48,#English,O
48,#Paper,O
48,pay,O
48,.,O
48,#Someone,O
48,help,O
48,paper,O
48,#Case,O
48,study,O
48,#essaypay,O
48,#Do,O
48,my,O
48,homework,O
48,#Online,O
48,class,O
48,#Religion,O
48,#book,O
48,review,O
48,#Assignment,O
48,#Chemistry,O
48,#History,O
48,Kindly,O
48,dm,O
48,us,O
48,rn,O
49,Hire,O
49,us,O
49,to,O
49,do,O
49,your,O
49,;,O
49,#Essays,O
49,#Test,O
49,#Anatomy,O
49,#English,O
49,#Programming,O
49,#Exams,O
49,#Political,O
49,science,O
49,#Finance,O
49,#Accounting,O
49,#History,O
49,#Projects,O
49,#Economics,O
49,#Business,O
49,#Statistics,O
49,#Calculus,O
49,#Quizzes,O
49,#Discussions,O
49,#Psychology,O
49,#Computer,O
49,#Theology,O
49,#movie,O
49,review,O
49,#Criminology,O
49,#Excel,O
49,https://t.co/k2TUP6OIFF,O
50,Hire,O
50,our,O
50,legit,O
50,services,O
50,in,O
50,;,O
50,#Math,O
50,#Chem,O
50,.,O
51,#Essay,O
51,due,O
51,.,O
52,.....,O
52,.,O
53,#Paper,O
53,write,O
53,#English,O
53,#Paper,O
53,pay,O
53,.,O
54,#Someone,O
54,help,O
54,paper,O
54,#Case,O
54,study,O
54,#essaypay,O
54,#Online,O
54,class,O
54,#Religion,O
54,#book,O
54,review,O
54,.,O
54,.,O
54,#Assignment,O
54,#Chemistry,O
54,#History,O
54,Kindly,O
54,dm,O
54,us,O
54,rn,O
55,Hire,O
55,our,O
55,legit,O
55,services,O
55,in,O
55,;,O
55,#Math,O
55,#Chem,O
55,.,O
56,#Essay,O
56,due,O
56,#Paper,O
56,write,O
56,#English,O
56,#Paper,O
56,pay,O
56,.,O
57,#Someone,O
57,help,O
57,paper,O
57,#Case,O
57,study,O
57,#essaypay,O
57,.........,O
57,.,O
57,#Online,O
57,class,O
57,#Religion,O
57,#book,O
57,review,O
57,.,O
57,.,O
57,#Assignment,O
57,#Chemistry,O
57,#History,O
57,Kindly,O
57,dm,O
57,us,O
57,rn,O
58,Hire,O
58,our,O
58,legit,O
58,services,O
58,in,O
58,;,O
58,#Math,O
58,#Chem,O
58,.,O
59,#Essay,O
59,due,O
59,#Paper,O
59,write,O
59,#English,O
59,#Paper,O
59,pay,O
59,.,O
60,#Someone,O
60,help,O
60,paper,O
60,#Case,O
60,study,O
60,#essaypay,O
60,#Online,O
60,class,O
60,.......,O
60,.,O
61,#Religion,O
61,#book,O
61,review,O
61,.,O
61,.,O
61,#Assignment,O
61,#Chemistry,O
61,#History,O
61,Kindly,O
61,dm,O
61,us,O
61,rn,O
62,On,O
62,this,O
62,day,O
62,in,O
62,1901,O
62,",",O
62,the,O
62,first,O
62,scheduled,O
62,train,B-VEH
62,to,O
62,carry,O
62,paying,B-PER
62,passengers,I-PER
62,on,O
62,the,O
62,Grand,B-ORG
62,Canyon,I-ORG
62,Railway,I-ORG
62,arrived,O
62,at,O
62,the,O
62,Grand,B-LOC
62,Canyon,I-LOC
62,South,I-LOC
62,Rim,I-LOC
62,.,O
63,Your,B-PER
63,students,I-PER
63,can,O
63,learn,O
63,more,O
63,about,O
63,the,O
63,Grand,B-LOC
63,Canyon,I-LOC
63,with,O
63,our,O
63,line,O
63,of,O
63,products,O
63,!,O
63,https://t.co/bFJdeplIhn,O
63,#history,O
63,#trains,B-VEH
63,#grandcanyon,B-LOC
63,https://t.co/7jVHHATBPD,O
64,Hire,O
64,our,O
64,legit,O
64,services,O
64,in,O
64,;,O
64,#Math,O
64,#Chem,O
64,.,O
65,#Essay,O
65,due,O
65,#Paper,O
65,write,O
65,#English,O
65,#Paper,O
65,pay,O
65,.,O
66,#Someone,O
66,help,O
66,paper,O
66,#Case,O
66,study,O
66,#essaypay,O
66,#Online,O
66,class,O
66,#Religion,O
66,#book,O
66,review........,O
66,...,O
66,#Assignment,O
66,#Chemistry,O
66,#History,O
66,Kindly,O
66,dm,O
66,us,O
66,rn,O
67,Hire,O
67,our,O
67,legit,O
67,services,O
67,in,O
67,;,O
67,#Math,O
67,#Chem,O
67,.,O
68,#Essay,O
68,due,O
68,#Paper,O
68,write,O
68,#English,O
68,#Paper,O
68,pay,O
68,.,O
69,#Someone,O
69,help,O
69,paper,O
69,#Case,O
69,study,O
69,#essaypay,O
69,#Online,O
69,class,O
69,#Religion,O
69,#book,O
69,review,O
69,.,O
69,.,O
70,#Assignment,O
70,#Chemistry.....,O
70,.,O
71,#History,O
71,Kindly,O
71,dm,O
71,us,O
71,rn,O
72,Hire,O
72,our,O
72,legit,O
72,services,O
72,in,O
72,;,O
72,#Math,O
72,#Chem,O
72,.,O
73,#Essay,O
73,due,O
73,#Paper,O
73,write,O
73,#English,O
73,#Paper,O
73,pay,O
73,.,O
74,#Someone,O
74,help,O
74,paper,O
74,#Case,O
74,study,O
74,#essaypay,O
74,#Online,O
74,class,O
74,#Religion,O
74,#book,O
74,review,O
74,.,O
74,.,O
75,#Assignment,O
75,#Chemistry,O
75,#History,O
75,Kindly,O
75,dm,O
75,us,O
75,rn.....,O
75,.,O
76,Hire,O
76,our,O
76,legit,O
76,services,O
76,in,O
76,;,O
76,#Math,O
76,#Chem,O
76,.,O
77,#Essay,O
77,due,O
77,#Paper,O
77,write,O
77,#English,O
77,#Paper,O
77,pay,O
77,.,O
78,#Someone,O
78,help,O
78,paper,O
78,#Case,O
78,study,O
78,#essaypay,O
78,#Online,O
78,class,O
78,#Religion,O
78,#book,O
78,review,O
78,.,O
78,.,O
79,#Assignment,O
79,#Chemistry,O
79,#History,O
79,Kindly,O
79,dm,O
79,us,O
79,rn,O
80,Today,O
80,#OTD,O
80,I,O
80,would,O
80,usually,O
80,post,O
80,about,O
80,the,O
80,anniversary,O
80,of,O
80,the,O
80,death,O
80,of,O
80,my,B-PER
80,great,I-PER
80,grandmother,I-PER
80,who,I-PER
80,was,I-PER
80,killed,I-PER
80,during,I-PER
80,the,I-PER
80,bombing,I-PER
80,of,I-PER
80,Mokot\xc3\xb3w,I-PER
80,.,O
81,However,O
81,",",O
81,I,O
81,found,O
81,new,O
81,evidence,O
81,during,O
81,my,O
81,research,O
81,that,O
81,today,O
81,was,O
81,not,O
81,the,O
81,actual,O
81,day,O
81,she,B-PER
81,died,O
81,but,O
81,a,O
81,few,O
81,days,O
81,later,O
81,.,O
81,#watchthisspace,O
81,#History,O
82,Morse,O
82,code,O
82,operation,O
82,#Video,O
82,of,O
82,NW7US,O
82,@,O
82,#radio,O
82,https://t.co/69t1LbyGSd,O
82,#CW,O
82,#SKCC,O
82,#history,O
82,#Morsecode,O
82,#spacewx,O
82,#hamr,O
82,#swl,O
83,Morse,O
83,code,O
83,operation,O
83,#Video,O
83,of,O
83,NW7US,O
83,@,O
83,#radio,O
83,https://t.co/WML0dOC5r8,O
83,#CW,O
83,#SKCC,O
83,#history,O
83,#Morsecode,O
83,#spacewx,O
83,#hamr,O
83,#swl,O
84,There\'s,O
84,a,O
84,lot,O
84,to,O
84,be,O
84,learned,O
84,within,O
84,this,O
84,wonderful,O
84,read,O
84,!,O
85,Grab,O
85,a,O
85,copy,O
85,of,O
85,Apocalypse...Whenever,O
85,now,O
85,.,O
85,#politics,O
85,#apocalypse,O
85,#socialscience,O
85,#history,O
85,#nonfiction,O
85,@kenmooney,B-PER
85,Buy,O
85,Now,O
85,--&gt,O
85,;,O
85,https://t.co/jPlUbW5Hjp,O
85,https://t.co/pSVCsXhsYD,O
86,English,B-PER
86,architect,I-PER
86,and,I-PER
86,archaeologist,I-PER
86,Charles,I-PER
86,Robert,I-PER
86,Cockerell,I-PER
86,",",O
86,who,O
86,died,O
86,OTD,O
86,in,O
86,1863,O
86,",",O
86,left,O
86,on,O
86,a,O
86,3-year,O
86,Grand,O
86,Tour,O
86,to,O
86,be,O
86,spent,O
86,mostly,O
86,in,O
86,#Greece,B-GPE
86,;,O
86,it,O
86,ended,O
86,up,O
86,lasting,O
86,7,O
86,years,O
86,https://t.co/2PO9EA87Sl,O
86,#travel,O
86,#history,O
87,Get,O
87,online,O
87,class,O
87,homework,O
87,",",O
87,assignment,O
87,exam,O
87,help,O
87,math,O
87,#pay,O
87,essay,O
87,#pay,O
87,homework,O
87,#pay,O
87,assignment,O
87,#pay,O
87,hw,O
87,#biology,O
87,#pay,O
87,online,O
87,class,O
87,#nursing,O
87,#lab,O
87,report,O
87,#economics,O
87,#history,O
87,.,O
87,#sociology,O
87,#Eassy,O
87,pay,O
87,#Eassy,O
87,Due,O
87,#USA,B-GPE
87,#Canada,B-GPE
87,#Australia,B-GPE
87,#Newzealand,B-GPE
87,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
87,#UAE,B-GPE
87,#Kuwait,B-GPE
87,#Germany,B-GPE
87,https://t.co/0rONmsSH5b,O
88,I,O
88,do,O
88,think,O
88,more,O
88,#humans,O
88,should,O
88,focus,O
88,on,O
88,studying,O
88,#science,O
88,rather,O
88,than,O
88,#history,O
88,\xe2\x80\xa6,O
88,though,O
88,both,O
88,are,O
88,important,O
89,Get,O
89,online,O
89,class,O
89,homework,O
89,",",O
89,assignment,O
89,exam,O
89,help,O
89,math,O
89,#pay,O
89,essay,O
89,#pay,O
89,homework,O
89,#pay,O
89,assignment,O
89,#pay,O
89,hw,O
89,#biology,O
89,#pay,O
89,online,O
89,class,O
89,#nursing,O
89,#lab,O
89,report,O
89,#economics,O
89,#history,O
89,.,O
89,#sociology,O
89,#Eassy,O
89,pay,O
89,#Eassy,O
89,Due,O
89,#USA,B-GPE
89,#Canada,B-GPE
89,#Australia,B-GPE
89,#Newzealand,B-GPE
89,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
89,#UAE,B-GPE
89,#Kuwait,B-GPE
89,#Germany,B-GPE
89,https://t.co/pIHQB77YPL,O
90,Get,O
90,online,O
90,class,O
90,homework,O
90,",",O
90,assignment,O
90,exam,O
90,help,O
90,math,O
90,#pay,O
90,essay,O
90,#pay,O
90,homework,O
90,#pay,O
90,assignment,O
90,#pay,O
90,hw,O
90,#biology,O
90,#pay,O
90,online,O
90,class,O
90,#nursing,O
90,#lab,O
90,report,O
90,#economics,O
90,#history,O
90,.,O
90,#sociology,O
90,#Eassy,O
90,pay,O
90,#Eassy,O
90,Due,O
90,#USA,B-GPE
90,#Canada,B-GPE
90,#Australia,B-GPE
90,#Newzealand,B-GPE
90,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
90,#UAE,B-GPE
90,#Kuwait,B-GPE
90,#Germany,B-GPE
90,https://t.co/pUevcFQilT,O
91,Get,O
91,online,O
91,class,O
91,homework,O
91,",",O
91,assignment,O
91,exam,O
91,help,O
91,math,O
91,#pay,O
91,essay,O
91,#pay,O
91,homework,O
91,#pay,O
91,assignment,O
91,#pay,O
91,hw,O
91,#biology,O
91,#pay,O
91,online,O
91,class,O
91,#nursing,O
91,#lab,O
91,report,O
91,#economics,O
91,#history,O
91,.,O
91,#sociology,O
91,#Eassy,O
91,pay,O
91,#Eassy,O
91,Due,O
91,#USA,B-GPE
91,#Canada,B-GPE
91,#Australia,B-GPE
91,#Newzealand,B-GPE
91,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
91,#UAE,B-GPE
91,#Kuwait,B-GPE
91,#Germany,B-GPE
91,https://t.co/yrqoZhTR6D,O
92,A,O
92,great,O
92,museum,B-FAC
92,to,O
92,visit,O
92,while,O
92,in,O
92,Boston,B-GPE
92,#art,O
92,#boston,B-GPE
92,#mass,I-GPE
92,#history,O
92,#finearts,O
92,@,O
92,Museum,B-FAC
92,of,I-FAC
92,Fine,I-FAC
92,Arts,I-FAC
92,",",O
92,Boston,B-GPE
92,https://t.co/RbNl860g4u,O
93,Get,O
93,online,O
93,class,O
93,homework,O
93,",",O
93,assignment,O
93,exam,O
93,help,O
93,math,O
93,#pay,O
93,essay,O
93,#pay,O
93,homework,O
93,#pay,O
93,assignment,O
93,#pay,O
93,hw,O
93,#biology,O
93,#pay,O
93,online,O
93,class,O
93,#nursing,O
93,#lab,O
93,report,O
93,#economics,O
93,#history,O
93,.,O
93,#sociology,O
93,#Eassy,O
93,pay,O
93,#Eassy,O
93,Due,O
93,#USA,B-GPE
93,#Canada,B-GPE
93,#Australia,B-GPE
93,#Newzealand,B-GPE
93,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
93,#UAE,B-GPE
93,#Kuwait,B-GPE
93,#Russia,B-GPE
93,https://t.co/eXb5bUcN1Q,O
94,Agios,B-LOC
94,Lavrentios:,I-LOC
94,The,O
94,Village,B-LOC
94,Untouched,O
94,by,O
94,Time,O
94,https://t.co/tqAAe43GhD,O
94,via,O
94,@greekcitytimes,B-ORG
94,#greece,B-GPE
94,#greek,B-GPE
94,#travel,O
94,#pelion,O
94,#History,O
95,Get,O
95,online,O
95,class,O
95,homework,O
95,",",O
95,assignment,O
95,exam,O
95,help,O
95,math,O
95,#pay,O
95,essay,O
95,#pay,O
95,homework,O
95,#pay,O
95,assignment,O
95,#pay,O
95,hw,O
95,#biology,O
95,#pay,O
95,online,O
95,class,O
95,#nursing,O
95,#lab,O
95,report,O
95,#economics,O
95,#history,O
95,.,O
95,#sociology,O
95,#Eassy,O
95,pay,O
95,#Eassy,O
95,Due,O
95,#USA,B-GPE
95,#Canada,B-GPE
95,#Australia,B-GPE
95,#Newzealand,B-GPE
95,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
95,#UAE,B-GPE
95,#Kuwait,B-GPE
95,#Germany,B-GPE
95,https://t.co/zQ9y4cASPg,O
96,Get,O
96,online,O
96,class,O
96,homework,O
96,",",O
96,assignment,O
96,exam,O
96,help,O
96,math,O
96,#pay,O
96,essay,O
96,#pay,O
96,homework,O
96,#pay,O
96,assignment,O
96,#pay,O
96,hw,O
96,#biology,O
96,#pay,O
96,online,O
96,class,O
96,#nursing,O
96,#lab,O
96,report,O
96,#economics,O
96,#history,O
96,.,O
96,#sociology,O
96,#Eassy,O
96,pay,O
96,#Eassy,O
96,Due,O
96,#USA,B-GPE
96,#Canada,B-GPE
96,#Australia,B-GPE
96,#Newzealand,B-GPE
96,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
96,#UAE,B-GPE
96,#Kuwait,B-GPE
96,#Germany,B-GPE
96,https://t.co/xfmuH3oQam,O
97,Small,O
97,time,O
97,mobster..,B-PER
97,.,O
97,#Prohibition,O
97,#history,O
97,https://t.co/hwJQaCuF1h,O
98,Get,O
98,online,O
98,class,O
98,homework,O
98,",",O
98,assignment,O
98,exam,O
98,help,O
98,math,O
98,#pay,O
98,essay,O
98,#pay,O
98,homework,O
98,#pay,O
98,assignment,O
98,#pay,O
98,hw,O
98,#biology,O
98,#pay,O
98,online,O
98,class,O
98,#nursing,O
98,#lab,O
98,report,O
98,#economics,O
98,#history,O
98,.,O
98,#sociology,O
98,#Eassy,O
98,pay,O
98,#Eassy,O
98,Due,O
98,#USA,B-GPE
98,#Canada,B-GPE
98,#Australia,B-GPE
98,#Newzealand,B-GPE
98,#UnitedKingdom,B-GPE
98,#UAE,B-GPE
98,#Kuwait,B-GPE
98,#Germany,B-GPE
99,The,O
99,grace,O
99,&amp,O
99,;,O
99,strength,O
99,with,O
99,which,O
99,#MeghanMarkel,B-PER
99,is,O
99,handling,O
99,the,O
99,racially,O
99,motivated,O
99,hatred,O
99,from,O
99,the,O
99,British,B-ORG
99,Press,I-ORG
99,&amp,O
99,;,O
99,jealous/bitter,O
99,white,B-PER
99,women,I-PER
99,will,O
99,only,O
99,make,O
99,her,B-PER
99,go,O
99,down,O
99,in,O
99,#History,O
99,as,O
99,a,O
99,symbolic,O
99,&amp,O
99,;,O
99,great,O
99,figure,O
99,of,O
99,our,O
99,time,O
99,.,O
100,Shooting,O
100,yourselves,O
100,in,O
100,the,O
100,foot,O
100,#karens,B-PER
100,!,O
101,Good,O
101,evening,O
101,dear,O
101,friends,B-PER
101,!,O
102,\xf0\x9f\xa4\x97,O
102,Trancoso,B-LOC
102,Castle,I-LOC
102,",",O
102,northeast,B-LOC
102,#Portugal,B-GPE
102,.,O
103,Nine,O
103,centuries,O
103,contemplate,O
103,this,O
103,landscape,O
103,.,O
104,It\xe2\x80\x99s,O
104,a,O
104,mountain,B-LOC
104,area,I-LOC
104,",",O
104,w/,O
104,many,O
104,plateaus,B-LOC
104,",",O
104,very,O
104,high,O
104,elevations,O
104,(up,O
104,to,O
104,985,O
104,meters),O
104,#travelphotography,O
104,#geography,O
104,#History,O
104,https://t.co/mXQHg5KDZQ,O
105,The,O
105,capitol,O
105,with,O
105,a,O
105,plenty,O
105,of,O
105,history,O
105,#dubuandmore,O
105,#dubuduro,B-GPE
105,#mexiko,I-GPE
105,#mexiko\xf0\x9f\x87\xb2\xf0\x9f\x87\xbd,I-GPE
105,#postoffice,B-FAC
105,#history,O
105,#oldtown,O
105,@,O
105,Mexico,B-GPE
105,City,I-GPE
105,",",O
105,Mexico,B-GPE
105,https://t.co/wW1nIAduRU,O
106,The,O
106,Roman,B-ORG
106,Empire,I-ORG
106,invaded,O
106,Ireland,B-GPE
106,and,O
106,took,O
106,Irish,B-PER
106,slaves,I-PER
106,to,O
106,work,O
106,the,O
106,agricultural,O
106,fields,O
106,of,O
106,Romano,B-GPE
106,Britain,I-GPE
106,.,O
107,#celticfilms,O
107,#IrelandCeltics,B-GPE
107,#BritainCeltics,B-GPE
107,#RomanEmpire,B-GPE
107,#Slavery,O
107,Druid,B-PER
107,Queen,I-PER
107,Maeve,I-PER
107,led,O
107,the,O
107,Celtic,B-ORG
107,armies,I-ORG
107,against,O
107,the,O
107,Roman,B-GPE
107,Empire,I-GPE
107,in,O
107,combat,O
107,in,O
107,Britain,B-GPE
107,itself,O
107,.,O
107,#history,O
107,https://t.co/BX3kIPKVNV,O
108,We,B-PER
108,are,O
108,often,O
108,told,O
108,how,O
108,Punjabi,B-GPE
108,dressing,O
108,has,O
108,deep,O
108,impact,O
108,of,O
108,Islamic,B-GPE
108,rule,O
108,but,O
108,the,O
108,fact,O
108,is,O
108,its,O
108,traditional,O
108,dressing,O
108,had,O
108,already,O
108,emerged,O
108,in,O
108,Pre,O
108,Islamic,B-GPE
108,period,O
108,as,O
108,one,O
108,can,O
108,see,O
108,from,O
108,these,O
108,sculptures,O
108,from,O
108,7th,O
108,to,O
108,9th,O
108,century,O
108,Kashmir,B-LOC
108,!,O
108,#History,O
108,@GemsOfIndology,B-PER
108,@PrasunNagar,B-PER
108,@Arthistorian18,B-PER
108,https://t.co/8JpmnlckF4,O
109,Film,B-PER
109,critic,I-PER
109,@bobross48,I-PER
109,on,O
109,Royalty,O
109,In,O
109,Movies,O
109,Tomorrow,O
109,",",O
109,Sunday,O
109,18,O
109,at,O
109,10,O
109,am,O
109,ET,O
109,on,O
109,https://t.co/hGIs5f8X8h,O
109,&amp,O
109,;,O
109,12,O
109,pm,O
109,ET,O
109,on,O
109,The,B-ORG
109,Source,I-ORG
109,HD3,O
109,https://t.co/Lw15Xfjrz5,O
109,Details,O
109,https://t.co/kewhGBn4m1,O
109,#talkshow,O
109,#films,O
109,#opinions,O
109,#history,O
109,#royalty,O
109,https://t.co/L8EwuL6fps,O
110,Emperor,B-PER
110,Uda,I-PER
110,",",O
110,59th,I-PER
110,Emperor,I-PER
110,of,O
110,#Japan,B-GPE
110,",",O
110,ascended,O
110,to,O
110,the,O
110,Chrysanthemum,B-LOC
110,Throne,I-LOC
110,OTD,O
110,in,O
110,887,O
110,https://t.co/PuNEMFSwF2,O
110,#travel,O
110,#history,O
111,Yes,O
111,.,O
112,History,O
112,contains,O
112,the,O
112,good,O
112,",",O
112,the,O
112,bad,O
112,",",O
112,and,O
112,the,O
112,ugly,O
112,.,O
113,If,O
113,you\xe2\x80\x99re,O
113,only,O
113,seeking,O
113,the,O
113,\xe2\x80\x9cgood\xe2\x80\x9d,O
113,you,O
113,aren\xe2\x80\x99t,O
113,learning,O
113,#History,O
113,",",O
113,you,O
113,are,O
113,experiencing,O
113,propaganda,O
113,.,O
113,https://t.co/tu68sZNFHt,O
114,Are,O
114,you,O
114,a,O
114,working,O
114,student,B-PER
114,?,O
115,Are,O
115,you,O
115,overwhelmed,O
115,by,O
115,online,O
115,classes,O
115,",",O
115,assignments,O
115,",",O
115,research,O
115,papers...DM,O
115,us,O
115,for,O
115,professional,O
115,help,O
115,#Assignments,O
115,#assignmentdue,O
115,#Nursing,O
115,#Biology,O
115,#Sociology,O
115,#business,O
115,#history,O
115,Pay,O
115,someone,O
115,@kuwait_tutors_,B-PER
116,Let,O
116,our,O
116,experts,O
116,handle,O
116,your,O
116,#Essay,O
116,due,O
116,#Online,O
116,Class,O
116,#Course,O
116,work,O
116,#Project,O
116,#Essay,O
116,due,O
116,#Pay,O
116,write,O
116,#econometrics,O
116,#Paperpay,O
116,#Someone,O
116,help,O
116,paper,O
116,#Case,O
116,study,O
116,#javascript,O
116,#History,O
116,#Homework.,O
116,.,O
117,",",O
117,.,O
118,#Philosophy,O
118,#Assignment,O
118,due,O
118,Pay,O
118,someone,O
118,write,O
118,@kuwait_tutors_,B-PER
119,#pay,O
119,hw,O
119,#pay,O
119,maths,O
119,#pay,O
119,chem,O
119,#biology,O
119,#mymathlab,O
119,#nursing,O
119,#lab,O
119,report,O
119,#economics,O
119,#history,O
119,#sociology,O
119,#anatomy,O
119,#research,O
119,#Eassy,O
119,pay,O
119,#Eassy,O
119,.,O
120,Order,O
120,here&gt,O
120,;&gt,O
120,;&gt,O
120,;,O
120,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
121,#history,O
121,Watch,O
121,the,O
121,Book,O
121,Trailer,O
121,for,O
121,Henry,B-PER
121,Knox's,I-PER
121,Noble,O
121,Train,B-VEH
121,JUST,O
121,RELEASED,O
121,https://t.co/zV0Kqq8HOW,O
122,I,O
122,discovered,O
122,the,O
122,Telephone,B-FAC
122,Museum,I-FAC
122,in,O
122,Maitland,B-GPE
122,",",O
122,FL,I-GPE
122,today,O
122,.,O
123,Very,O
123,cool,O
123,history,O
123,and,O
123,artifacts,O
123,on,O
123,display,O
123,!,O
123,@AHmaitland,B-PER
123,#museum,B-FAC
123,#history,O
123,#localhistory,O
123,#telephone,O
123,#LoveFL,O
123,https://t.co/jrzLysTkag,O
124,#economics,O
124,#history,O
124,#sociology,O
124,#anatomy,O
124,#research,O
124,#Eassy,O
124,pay,O
124,#Eassy,O
124,.,O
125,Order,O
125,here&gt,O
125,;&gt,O
125,;&gt,O
125,;,O
125,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
126,A,O
126,miniature,O
126,depicting,O
126,the,O
126,proclamation,O
126,of,O
126,Leo,B-PER
126,V,I-PER
126,the,O
126,Armenian,B-GPE
126,as,O
126,emperor,B-PER
126,(from,O
126,the,O
126,Madrid,B-GPE
126,Skylitzes),O
126,.,O
127,Leo,B-PER
127,V,I-PER
127,is,I-PER
127,the,I-PER
127,only,I-PER
127,Byzantine,I-PER
127,emperor,I-PER
127,to,O
127,be,O
127,nicknamed,O
127,Armenian,B-GPE
127,by,O
127,Byzantine,B-GPE
127,chroniclers,B-PER
127,.,O
127,#Armenia,B-GPE
127,#History,O
127,#Byzantium,B-GPE
127,https://t.co/UQZRkd3qiu,O
128,History,O
128,of,O
128,Australia:,B-GPE
128,4-PART,O
128,BUNDLE,O
128,(120,O
128,slides,O
128,with,O
128,5,O
128,pages,O
128,of,O
128,guided,O
128,notes),O
128,https://t.co/DrRqARRCIc,O
128,#Austrailia,B-GPE
128,#Teachertwitter,O
128,#teachersday,O
128,#lessons,O
128,#easytouse,O
128,#downloadtoday,O
128,#mapping,O
128,#history,O
128,#geography,O
128,#lessonshop,O
129,#nursing,O
129,#lab,O
129,report,O
129,#economics,O
129,#history,O
129,#sociology,O
129,#anatomy,O
129,#research,O
129,#Eassy,O
129,pay,O
129,#Eassy,O
129,.,O
130,#NodeJS,O
130,#IoT,O
130,#Python,O
130,#100DaysOfCode,O
130,DM,O
130,@academic334,B-PER
130,Order,O
130,here&gt,O
130,;&gt,O
130,;&gt,O
130,;,O
130,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
131,#nursing,O
131,#lab,O
131,report,O
131,#economics,O
131,#history,O
131,#sociology,O
131,#anatomy,O
131,#research,O
131,#Eassy,O
131,pay,O
131,#Eassy,O
131,.,O
132,#NodeJS,O
132,#IoT,O
132,#Python,O
132,#100DaysOfCode,O
132,DM,O
132,@academic334,B-PER
133,#pay,O
133,chem,O
133,#biology,O
133,#mymathlab,O
133,#nursing,O
133,#lab,O
133,report,O
133,#economics,O
133,#history,O
133,#sociology,O
133,#anatomy,O
133,#research,O
133,Order,O
133,here&gt,O
133,;&gt,O
133,;&gt,O
133,;,O
133,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
134,#pay,O
134,chem,O
134,#biology,O
134,#mymathlab,O
134,#nursing,O
134,#lab,O
134,report,O
134,#economics,O
134,#history,O
134,#sociology,O
134,#anatomy,O
134,#research,O
135,[],O
135,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6[the,O
135,WWII,O
135,Gen,O
135,have,O
135,been,O
135,fighting,O
135,back,O
135,with,O
135,all,O
135,the,O
135,firepower,O
135,they,O
135,can,O
135,muster],O
135,against,O
135,realizing,O
135,the,O
135,harsh,O
135,realities,O
135,around,O
135,them,O
135,of,O
135,their,O
135,waning,O
135,ideals.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
135,[],O
135,THREAD,O
135,https://t.co/nFbKtM8O0Y,O
135,#Midterms,O
135,#FBR,O
135,#generations,O
135,#resist,O
135,#culture,O
135,#rebirth,O
135,#psychology,O
135,#history,O
135,CW22,O
135,13424,O
136,Searching,O
136,for,O
136,Room,B-FAC
136,41,I-FAC
136,-,O
136,homework,O
136,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
136,#art,O
136,#history,O
136,#culture,O
136,#roman,B-GPE
136,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
136,#suttonhoo,O
136,#celtic,B-GPE
136,#gold,O
136,#museum,B-FAC
136,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
136,https://t.co/hRabQH4HzH,O
137,Searching,O
137,for,O
137,Room,B-FAC
137,41,I-FAC
137,-,O
137,homework,O
137,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
137,#art,O
137,#history,O
137,#culture,O
137,#roman,B-GPE
137,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
137,#suttonhoo,O
137,#celtic,B-GPE
137,#gold,O
137,#museum,B-FAC
137,#runic,O
137,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
137,https://t.co/di64wAc2ty,O
138,#paper,O
138,pay,O
138,#stats,O
138,#hw,O
138,#Do,O
138,my,O
138,homework,O
138,#Online,O
138,class,O
138,#Assignment,O
138,due,O
138,#History,O
138,#javascript,O
138,#calculus,O
138,....,O
138,.,O
139,#Dissertations,O
139,Order,O
139,here&gt,O
139,;&gt,O
139,;&gt,O
139,;,O
139,https://t.co/KTstIYR7AH,O
140,#paper,O
140,pay,O
140,#stats,O
140,#hw,O
140,#Do,O
140,my,O
140,homework,O
140,#Online,O
140,class,O
140,#Assignment,O
140,due,O
140,#History,O
140,#javascript,O
140,#calculus,O
140,....,O
140,.,O
140,#Dissertations,O
141,Did,O
141,ancient,O
141,peoples,O
141,know,O
141,their,O
141,history,O
141,?,O
142,As,O
142,myth,O
142,and,O
142,#history,O
142,intertwine,O
142,",",O
142,@wellerstein,B-PER
142,explores,O
142,how,O
142,everyone,O
142,knows,O
142,their,O
142,past,O
142,in,O
142,a,O
142,sense,O
142,and,O
142,pass,O
142,on,O
142,historical,O
142,stories,O
142,.,O
142,#Twitterstorians,O
142,https://t.co/nWNNo1tiAy,O
143,\xf0\x9f\x93\x85#OnThisDay,O
143,",",O
143,Sept,O
143,17,O
143,",",O
143,77.5833333333333,O
143,At,O
143,the,O
143,Battle,B-LOC
143,of,I-LOC
143,#Antietam,B-LOC
143,",",O
143,Confederate,B-ORG
143,Gen.,B-PER
143,Robert,I-PER
143,E.,I-PER
143,Lee\xe2\x80\x99s,I-PER
143,Army,B-ORG
143,and,O
143,Union,B-ORG
143,Gen.,B-PER
143,George,I-PER
143,B.,I-PER
143,McClellan\xe2\x80\x99s,I-PER
143,Army,B-ORG
143,fight,O
143,to,O
143,a,O
143,standstill,O
143,along,O
143,a,O
143,Maryland,B-GPE
143,creek,B-LOC
143,.,O
144,23000,O
144,soldiers,O
144,are,O
144,killed,O
144,and,O
144,the,O
144,course,O
144,of,O
144,the,O
144,#CivilWar,O
144,is,O
144,changed,O
144,.,O
144,#history,O
144,\xf0\x9f\x93\xb7Public,O
144,domain,O
144,https://t.co/8ipLYfLnqB,O
145,Searching,O
145,for,O
145,Room,B-FAC
145,41,I-FAC
145,-,O
145,homework,O
145,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
145,#art,O
145,#history,O
145,#culture,O
145,#roman,B-GPE
145,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
145,#suttonhoo,O
145,#celtic,O
145,#gold,B-GPE
145,#museum,B-FAC
145,#torc,O
145,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
145,https://t.co/rAXC2EFLoe,O
146,Searching,O
146,for,O
146,Room,B-FAC
146,41,I-FAC
146,-,O
146,homework,O
146,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
146,#art,O
146,#history,O
146,#culture,O
146,#mesoamerica,O
146,#codex,O
146,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
146,https://t.co/DWijZQOogL,O
147,[],O
147,\xe2\x80\x9cSpecifically,O
147,",",O
147,I,O
147,am,O
147,saying,O
147,that,O
147,there,O
147,are,O
147,few,O
147,of,O
147,the,O
147,Sixties,O
147,Generation,O
147,who,O
147,would,O
147,not,O
147,classify,O
147,themselves,O
147,as,O
147,\xe2\x80\x9cpro-choice.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
147,[],O
147,READ,O
147,&amp,O
147,;/or,O
147,dwnld,O
147,entire,O
147,BOOK,O
147,free,O
147,AT,O
147,SITE..,O
147,.,O
148,https://t.co/N5aLZ2YaF4,O
148,#Midterms,O
148,#generations,O
148,#resist,O
148,#culture,O
148,#rebirth,O
148,#psychology,O
148,#history,O
148,CW22,O
148,44865,O
149,Pabon,O
149,.,O
150,Fought,O
150,September,O
150,17,O
150,",",O
150,1861,O
150,",",O
150,161,O
150,years,O
150,ago,O
150,",",O
150,#war,O
150,#history\xc2\xa0#event,O
150,https://t.co/1gQsp1pQKg,O
151,Pabon,O
151,.,O
152,Fought,O
152,September,O
152,17,O
152,",",O
152,1861,O
152,",",O
152,161,O
152,years,O
152,ago,O
152,",",O
152,#war,O
152,#history\xc2\xa0#event,O
152,https://t.co/OS7cvbebOX,O
153,#OTD,O
153,in,O
153,1857,O
153,",",O
153,Konstantin,B-PER
153,Eduardovich,I-PER
153,Tsiolkovsky,I-PER
153,",",O
153,a,O
153,Russian,B-GPE
153,schoolteacher,I-PER
153,and,I-PER
153,aeronautics,I-PER
153,and,I-PER
153,rocket,I-PER
153,scientist,I-PER
153,",",O
153,was,O
153,born,O
153,.,O
154,He,B-PER
154,derived,O
154,the,O
154,rocket,O
154,equation,O
154,and,O
154,published,O
154,it,O
154,in,O
154,1903,O
154,.,O
155,Tsiolkovsky,B-PER
155,is,O
155,considered,O
155,one,O
155,of,O
155,the,O
155,founding,B-PER
155,fathers,I-PER
155,of,I-PER
155,rocketry,I-PER
155,and,I-PER
155,astronautics,I-PER
155,.,O
155,#History,O
155,https://t.co/LdKAsnzZCx,O
156,[],O
156,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6your,O
156,position,O
156,on,O
156,the,O
156,abortion,O
156,issue,O
156,is,O
156,the,O
156,closest,O
156,thing,O
156,to,O
156,a,O
156,military,O
156,uniform,O
156,indicating,O
156,on,O
156,which,O
156,side,O
156,of,O
156,the,O
156,culture,O
156,war,O
156,you,O
156,have,O
156,enlisted.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
156,[],O
156,THREAD,O
156,https://t.co/nFbKtM8O0Y,O
156,#Midterms,O
156,#FBR,O
156,#generations,O
156,#resist,O
156,#culture,O
156,#rebirth,O
156,#psychology,O
156,#history,O
156,#WWIIGen,O
156,CW22,O
156,44864,O
157,Searching,O
157,for,O
157,Room,B-FAC
157,41,I-FAC
157,-,O
157,homework,O
157,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
157,#art,O
157,#history,O
157,#culture,O
157,#roman,B-GPE
157,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
157,#suttonhoo,O
157,#celtic,B-GPE
157,#gold,O
157,#museum,B-FAC
157,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
157,https://t.co/XfAZz7h3qV,O
158,I,O
158,can,O
158,handle,O
158,your,O
158,due,O
158,essay,O
158,at,O
158,Fair,O
158,price,O
158,.,O
159,#pay,O
159,homework,O
159,#pay,O
159,assignments,O
159,#pay,O
159,hw,O
159,#pay,O
159,maths,O
159,#pay,O
159,chem,O
159,#biology,O
159,#mymathlab,O
159,#nursing,O
159,#lab,O
159,report,O
159,#economics,O
159,#history,O
159,#sociology,O
159,#anatomy,O
159,#research,O
159,#Eassy,O
159,pay,O
159,#Eassy,O
159,DM,O
159,now,O
159,https://t.co/1ILIiL252d,O
160,[],O
160,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6[the,O
160,WWII,O
160,Gen,O
160,used,O
160,their,O
160,unprecedented,O
160,wealth,O
160,&amp,O
160,;,O
160,power,O
160,to,O
160,wage,O
160,a,O
160,war,O
160,the,O
160,60s,O
160,Generation],O
160,keeping,O
160,them,O
160,&amp,O
160,;,O
160,their,O
160,values,O
160,under,O
160,attack,O
160,&amp,O
160,;,O
160,away,O
160,from,O
160,the,O
160,centers,O
160,of,O
160,power,O
160,&amp,O
160,;,O
160,influence,O
160,in,O
160,society,O
160,as,O
160,long,O
160,as,O
160,they,O
160,possibly,O
160,could.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
160,[],O
160,THREAD,O
160,https://t.co/N5aLZ2YaF4,O
160,#history,O
160,CW22,O
160,44863,O
161,Searching,O
161,for,O
161,Room,O
161,41,I-FAC
161,-,O
161,homework,O
161,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
161,#art,O
161,#history,O
161,#culture,O
161,#roman,B-GPE
161,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
161,#suttonhoo,O
161,#celtic,B-GPE
161,#gold,O
161,#museum,B-FAC
161,#folktondrums,O
161,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
161,https://t.co/KPmsDdZIGk,O
162,Searching,O
162,for,O
162,Room,B-FAC
162,41,I-FAC
162,-,O
162,homework,O
162,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
162,#art,O
162,#history,O
162,#culture,O
162,#roman,B-GPE
162,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
162,#suttonhoo,O
162,#celtic,B-GPE
162,#gold,O
162,#museum,B-FAC
162,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
162,https://t.co/IoCw65ZiJT,O
163,Political,O
163,Cartoon,O
163,.,O
164,The,O
164,Soviet,B-ORG
164,Red,I-ORG
164,Army,I-ORG
164,invaded,O
164,Poland,B-GPE
164,#TDIH,O
164,in,O
164,1939,O
164,after,O
164,the,O
164,German,B-ORG
164,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
164,crossed,O
164,the,O
164,Polish,B-GPE
164,border,O
164,.,O
165,German-Soviet,B-GPE
165,collusion,O
165,shaped,O
165,the,O
165,Second,O
165,World,O
165,War,O
165,until,O
165,the,O
165,surprise,O
165,Nazi,B-ORG
165,invasion,O
165,of,O
165,the,O
165,Soviet,B-GPE
165,Union,I-GPE
165,in,O
165,1941,O
165,.,O
166,Miami,B-ORG
166,Herald,I-ORG
166,",",O
166,June,O
166,24,O
166,",",O
166,1941,O
166,.,O
166,#history,O
166,#OTD,O
166,https://t.co/1ACb5SFSEz,O
167,Searching,O
167,for,O
167,Room,B-FAC
167,41,I-FAC
167,-,O
167,homework,O
167,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
167,#art,O
167,#history,O
167,#culture,O
167,#roman,B-GPE
167,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
167,#suttonhoo,O
167,#celtic,B-GPE
167,#gold,O
167,#museum,B-FAC
167,https://t.co/rl6PvIJTcw,O
168,Pre-save,O
168,my,O
168,new,O
168,album,O
168,To,O
168,The,O
168,End,O
168,They,O
168,Remain,O
168,on,O
168,Spotify:,O
168,https://t.co/WZ70F8CsUF,O
168,(powered,O
168,by,O
168,@distrokid),B-PER
168,#History,O
168,#WW1,O
168,#Music,O
168,#HipHop,O
168,#Rap,O
168,#Education,O
168,#IndieMusic,O
168,#Spotify,O
169,Capt,O
169,.,O
170,Hondo,B-PER
170,Stone,I-PER
170,is,O
170,a,O
170,pistol-fighting,O
170,Texas,B-PER
170,Ranger,I-PER
170,who,O
170,serves,O
170,justice,O
170,6,O
170,blazing,O
170,shots,O
170,at,O
170,a,O
170,time,O
170,in,O
170,the,O
170,Wild,O
170,Western,O
170,novel,O
170,Old,O
170,San,O
170,Antone,O
170,.,O
171,Read,O
171,about,O
171,his,B-PER
171,exploits,O
171,on,O
171,#Kindle,O
171,!,O
171,https://t.co/d5yX6slx1H,O
171,#writersoftwitter,O
171,#HistoricalFiction,O
171,#History,O
171,#Entertainment,O
171,#BooksWorthReading,O
172,17,O
172,Sept,O
172,80.7916666666667,O
172,The,O
172,#Soviet,B-GPE
172,Union,I-GPE
172,invades,O
172,#Poland,B-GPE
172,during,O
172,the,O
172,Polish,B-GPE
172,Defensive,O
172,War,O
172,of,O
172,1939,O
172,.,O
173,Nazi,B-ORG
173,#Germany,B-GPE
173,invaded,O
173,on,O
173,September,O
173,1,O
173,",",O
173,beginning,O
173,World,O
173,War,O
173,II,O
173,in,O
173,#Europe,B-LOC
173,.,O
173,#WWII,O
173,#WW2,O
173,#OTD,O
173,#history,O
173,#ad,O
173,https://t.co/L0GttG3fqF,O
173,https://t.co/mjsVB22i5g,O
173,https://t.co/t3g4EfheQM,O
174,Searching,O
174,for,O
174,Room,B-FAC
174,41,I-FAC
174,-,O
174,homework,O
174,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
174,#art,O
174,#history,O
174,#culture,O
174,#roman,B-GPE
174,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
174,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
174,#celtic,B-GPE
174,#gold,O
174,#museum,B-FAC
174,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
174,https://t.co/4SH8krYF9t,O
175,The,O
175,first,O
175,step,O
175,in,O
175,eliminating,O
175,people,O
175,"""",O
175,says,O
175,Hubble,B-PER
175,",",O
175,is,O
175,to,O
175,erase,O
175,their,O
175,memory,O
175,.,O
176,Destroy,O
176,their,O
176,books,O
176,",",O
176,their,O
176,culture,O
176,",",O
176,their,O
176,history,O
176,",",O
176,Then,O
176,ask,O
176,someone,O
176,to,O
176,write,O
176,new,O
176,books,O
176,",",O
176,to,O
176,create,O
176,is,O
176,Hit,O
176,me,O
176,up,O
176,for,O
176,all,O
176,your,O
176,essays/assignments,O
176,due,O
176,;,O
176,essay,O
176,due,O
176,#finance,O
176,paper,O
176,pay,O
176,do,O
176,my,O
176,homework,O
176,.,O
177,#online,O
177,class,O
177,.,O
178,essay,O
178,pay,O
178,.,O
179,English,O
179,#history,O
179,coursework,O
179,.,O
180,philosophy,O
180,calculus,O
180,Dm,O
180,@Onlineclassesh6,B-PER
181,Searching,O
181,for,O
181,Room,B-FAC
181,41,I-FAC
181,-,O
181,homework,O
181,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
181,#art,O
181,#history,O
181,#culture,O
181,#roman,B-GPE
181,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
181,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
181,#celtic,B-GPE
181,#gold,O
181,#museum,B-FAC
181,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
181,https://t.co/ffZngVMKv5,O
182,Political,O
182,Cartoon,O
182,.,O
183,The,O
183,Soviet,B-ORG
183,Red,I-ORG
183,Army,I-ORG
183,invaded,O
183,Poland,B-GPE
183,#TDIH,O
183,in,O
183,1939,O
183,after,O
183,the,O
183,German,B-ORG
183,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
183,crossed,O
183,the,O
183,Polish,B-GPE
183,border,O
183,.,O
184,German-Soviet,B-GPE
184,collusion,O
184,shaped,O
184,the,O
184,Second,O
184,World,O
184,War,O
184,until,O
184,the,O
184,surprise,O
184,Nazi,B-ORG
184,invasion,O
184,of,O
184,the,O
184,Soviet,B-GPE
184,Union,I-GPE
184,.,O
185,Detroit,B-ORG
185,Free,I-ORG
185,Press,I-ORG
185,",",O
185,June,O
185,24,O
185,",",O
185,1941,O
185,.,O
185,#history,O
185,#OTD,O
185,https://t.co/k3ef29L61m,O
186,[],O
186,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6the,O
186,World,O
186,War,O
186,Two,O
186,Generation,O
186,used,O
186,their,O
186,longevity,O
186,for,O
186,all,O
186,their,O
186,worth,O
186,to,O
186,block,O
186,the,O
186,ascendancy,O
186,of,O
186,their,O
186,successors.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
186,[],O
186,READ,O
186,&amp,O
186,;/or,O
186,dwnld,O
186,entire,O
186,BOOK,O
186,free,O
186,AT,O
186,SITE..,O
186,.,O
186,https://t.co/nFbKtM8O0Y,O
186,#Midterms,O
186,#FBR,O
186,#generations,O
186,#resist,O
186,#culture,O
186,#rebirth,O
186,#psychology,O
186,#history,O
186,CW22,O
186,44860,O
187,Searching,O
187,for,O
187,Room,B-FAC
187,41,I-FAC
187,-,O
187,homework,O
187,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
187,#art,O
187,#history,O
187,#culture,O
187,#roman,B-GPE
187,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
187,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
187,#celtic,B-GPE
187,#gold,O
187,#museum,B-FAC
187,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
187,https://t.co/laYb9k34TM,O
188,@carjaw,B-PER
188,#Iran,B-GPE
188,#Presstv,O
188,#Hamas,B-ORG
188,#IslamicJihad,O
188,#Hezbollah,B-ORG
188,#UN,B-ORG
188,#US,B-GPE
188,#ISRAEL,B-GPE
188,Do,O
188,not,O
188,stop,O
188,about,O
188,#Palestine'ian,B-GPE
188,#History,O
188,and,O
188,#Jews,B-GPE
188,which,O
188,ORIGINATED,O
188,there,O
188,https://t.co/IfzY6uECn9,O
189,Use,O
189,our,O
189,#Museum,B-FAC
189,Directory,O
189,to,O
189,discover,O
189,#Milwaukee's,B-GPE
189,fantastic,O
189,#museums,B-FAC
189,!,O
190,Choose,O
190,#art,O
190,#science,O
190,#history,O
190,#nature,O
190,more,O
190,!,O
190,https://t.co/xjwMZrLBMC,O
190,#MKE,O
190,#sightseeing,O
190,#travel,O
190,https://t.co/XmbFo3Z59V,O
191,Searching,O
191,for,O
191,Room,B-FAC
191,41,I-FAC
191,-,O
191,homework,O
191,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
191,#art,O
191,#history,O
191,#culture,O
191,#roman,B-GPE
191,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
191,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
191,#celtic,B-GPE
191,#gold,O
191,#museum,B-FAC
191,#hoard,O
191,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
191,https://t.co/0LVomILunY,O
192,Searching,O
192,for,O
192,Room,B-FAC
192,41,I-FAC
192,-,O
192,homework,O
192,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
192,#art,O
192,#history,O
192,#culture,O
192,#roman,B-GPE
192,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
192,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
192,#celtic,B-GPE
192,#gold,O
192,#museum,B-FAC
192,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
192,https://t.co/vN7swMfCWj,O
193,Political,O
193,Cartoon,O
193,.,O
194,The,O
194,Soviet,B-ORG
194,Red,I-ORG
194,Army,I-ORG
194,invaded,O
194,Poland,B-GPE
194,#TDIH,O
194,in,O
194,1939,O
194,after,O
194,the,O
194,German,B-ORG
194,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
194,crossed,O
194,the,O
194,Polish,B-GPE
194,border,O
194,.,O
195,German-Soviet,B-GPE
195,collusion,O
195,shaped,O
195,the,O
195,Second,O
195,World,O
195,War,O
195,until,O
195,the,O
195,Nazi,B-ORG
195,invasion,O
195,of,O
195,the,O
195,Soviet,B-GPE
195,Union,I-GPE
195,.,O
196,Raleigh,B-ORG
196,News,I-ORG
196,and,I-ORG
196,Observer,I-ORG
196,",",O
196,September,O
196,18,O
196,",",O
196,1939,O
196,.,O
196,#history,O
196,#OTD,O
196,https://t.co/3fZHEIxSRL,O
197,Hit,O
197,me,O
197,up,O
197,for,O
197,all,O
197,your,O
197,essays/assignments,O
197,due,O
197,;,O
197,essay,O
197,due,O
197,#finance,O
197,paper,O
197,pay,O
197,do,O
197,my,O
197,homework,O
197,.,O
198,#online,O
198,class,O
198,.,O
199,essay,O
199,pay,O
199,.,O
200,English,O
200,#history,O
200,coursework,O
200,.,O
201,philosophy,O
201,calculus,O
201,Dm,O
201,@TutorsStates,B-PER
201,Email,O
201,advancedwriter36@gmail.com,O
201,https://t.co/YT7YLhCPg1,O
202,These,O
202,are,O
202,thought-provoking,O
202,",",O
202,cautionary,O
202,tales,O
202,from,O
202,the,O
202,pinnacle,O
202,of,O
202,the,O
202,American,B-GPE
202,literary,O
202,cannon,O
202,That,O
202,these,O
202,are,O
202,the,O
202,most,O
202,banned,O
202,books,O
202,tells,O
202,us,O
202,something,O
202,chilling,O
202,about,O
202,the,O
202,people,O
202,who,O
202,want,O
202,them,O
202,banned,O
202,#History,O
202,#Truth,O
202,#FirstAmendment,O
202,#education,O
202,#DemocracyNotAutocracy,O
202,https://t.co/orJ5A0qcIp,O
203,Searching,O
203,for,O
203,Room,B-FAC
203,41,I-FAC
203,-,O
203,homework,O
203,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
203,#art,O
203,#history,O
203,#culture,O
203,#roman,B-GPE
203,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
203,#suttonhoo,B-LOC
203,#celtic,B-GPE
203,#gold,O
203,#museum,B-FAC
203,#room41,B-FAC
203,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
203,https://t.co/WuJThDt9OZ,O
204,17,O
204,Sep1787,O
204,Philadelphia,B-GPE
204,",",I-GPE
204,PA,I-GPE
204,Constitutional,B-ORG
204,Convention,I-ORG
204,signed,O
204,the,O
204,final,O
204,draft,O
204,of,O
204,the,O
204,Constitution,O
204,.,O
205,The,O
205,product,O
205,of,O
205,four,O
205,months,O
205,of,O
205,secret,O
205,debate,O
205,",",O
205,it,O
205,replaced,O
205,the,O
205,Articles,O
205,of,O
205,Confederation,O
205,and,O
205,proposed,O
205,an,O
205,entirely,O
205,new,O
205,form,O
205,of,O
205,government,O
205,.,O
205,#RevWar,O
205,#History,O
205,#AmRev,O
205,https://t.co/6QscLBeQBe,O
206,Searching,O
206,for,O
206,Room,B-FAC
206,41,I-FAC
206,-,O
206,homework,O
206,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a,O
206,#art,O
206,#history,O
206,#culture,O
206,#roman,B-GPE
206,#anglosaxon,B-GPE
206,#suttonhoo,O
206,#celtic,B-GPE
206,#gold,O
206,#museum,B-FAC
206,@BritishMuseum,B-ORG
206,https://t.co/R4634V48o9,O
207,Congratulation\xe2\x80\x99s,O
207,to,O
207,@PalmNft,B-PER
207,&amp,O
207,;,O
207,@TheDCUniverse,B-ORG
207,on,O
207,your,O
207,FIRST,O
207,ever,O
207,DC,O
207,comic,O
207,book,O
207,on,O
207,the,O
207,blockchain,O
207,.,O
208,\xf0\x9f\x91\x8f,O
208,\xf0\x9f\xa6\x87,O
208,#nft,O
208,#batman,O
208,#BatmanDay,O
208,#blockchain,O
208,#history,O
208,https://t.co/B7eyUmcd7W,O
209,#paper,O
209,pay,O
209,#stats,O
209,#hw,O
209,#Do,O
209,my,O
209,homework,O
209,#Online,O
209,class,O
209,#Assignment,O
209,due,O
209,#History,O
209,#javascript,O
209,Order,O
209,here&gt,O
209,;&gt,O
209,;&gt,O
209,;,O
209,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
210,#paper,O
210,pay,O
210,#stats,O
210,#hw,O
210,#Do,O
210,my,O
210,homework,O
210,#Online,O
210,class,O
210,#Assignment,O
210,due,O
210,#History,O
210,#javascript,O
211,#Do,O
211,my,O
211,homework,O
211,#Online,O
211,class,O
211,#Assignment,O
211,due,O
211,#History,O
211,#javascript,O
211,#calculus,O
211,....,O
211,.,O
212,#Dissertations,O
212,Order,O
212,here&gt,O
212,;&gt,O
212,;&gt,O
212,;,O
212,https://t.co/KTstIYQzL9,O
213,My,O
213,presentation,O
213,@AlgomaU,B-PER
213,was,O
213,awesome,O
213,!,O
213,!,O
214,Thank,O
214,you,O
214,to,O
214,everyone,O
214,who,O
214,came,O
214,out,O
214,.,O
215,Room,B-FAC
215,was,O
215,at,O
215,full,O
215,capacity,O
215,!,O
216,Special,O
216,thanks,O
216,to,O
216,@bdouville,B-PER
216,for,O
216,helping,O
216,arrange,O
216,everything,O
216,and,O
216,for,O
216,letting,O
216,me,O
216,stay,O
216,at,O
216,his,B-PER
216,house,B-FAC
216,.,O
217,It,O
217,was,O
217,inspiring,O
217,to,O
217,connect,O
217,with,O
217,young,O
217,and,O
217,old,O
217,alike,O
217,.,O
217,#furtrade,O
217,#history,O
217,#music,O
217,https://t.co/EJsKIfxbuZ,O
218,#OnThisDay,O
218,in,O
218,#history---a,O
218,slaver,B-PER
218,just,O
218,bought,O
218,a,O
218,human,B-PER
218,being's,I-PER
218,grandchild,I-PER
218,.,O
218,https://t.co/rh3nHvk8V8,O
218,I,O
218,can,O
218,handle,O
218,your,O
218,due,O
218,essay,O
218,at,O
218,Fair,O
218,price,O
218,.,O
219,#pay,O
219,homework,O
219,#pay,O
219,assignments,O
219,#pay,O
219,hw,O
219,#pay,O
219,maths,O
219,#pay,O
219,chem,O
219,#biology,O
219,#mymathlab,O
219,#nursing,O
219,#lab,O
219,report,O
219,@Pay_Writters,B-PER
219,#economics,O
219,#history,O
219,#sociology,O
219,#anatomy,O
219,#research,O
219,#Eassy,O
219,pay,O
219,#Eassy,O
219,Email,O
219,paywritters@gmail.com,O
220,Hit,O
220,me,O
220,up,O
220,for,O
220,all,O
220,your,O
220,essays/assignments,O
220,due,O
220,;,O
220,essay,O
220,due,O
220,#finance,O
220,paper,O
220,pay,O
220,do,O
220,my,O
220,homework,O
220,.,O
221,#online,O
221,class,O
221,.,O
222,essay,O
222,pay,O
222,.,O
223,English,O
223,#history,O
223,coursework,O
223,.,O
224,philosophy,O
224,calculus,O
224,Dm,O
224,@Pay_Writters,B-PER
224,Email,O
224,paywritters@gmail.com,O
224,https://t.co/F3qnx4XiXL,O
225,Period,O
225,dramas,O
225,should,O
225,not,O
225,be,O
225,judged,O
225,on,O
225,#historical,O
225,accuracy,O
225,",",O
225,say,O
225,#historians,B-PER
225,https://t.co/hS1AAdRAMr,O
225,I,O
225,agree,O
225,more,O
225,with,O
225,the,O
225,2nd,O
225,#historian,B-PER
225,that,O
225,explains,O
225,drama,O
225,has,O
225,a,O
225,responsibility,O
225,to,O
225,be,O
225,at,O
225,least,O
225,engaging,O
225,with,O
225,#history.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
225,#Books,O
225,should,O
225,be,O
225,the,O
225,same,O
225,!,O
226,A,O
226,Curtsy,O
226,For,O
226,A,O
226,Dead,O
226,Queen,B-PER
226,https://t.co/LYLHBgTsbr,O
226,#QueenElizabeth,B-PER
226,#QueenElizabethIIMemorial,O
226,#History,O
226,#Respect,O
227,Today,O
227,in,O
227,#History,O
227,the,O
227,US,O
227,Constitution,O
227,was,O
227,ratified,O
227,by,O
227,the,O
227,states,O
227,",",O
227,which,O
227,kind,O
227,of,O
227,makes,O
227,today,O
227,our,O
227,government's,O
227,birthday,O
227,.,O
228,Happy,O
228,birthday,O
228,",",O
228,gov,O
228,.,O
228,#ConstitutionDay,O
228,#TheMoreYouKnow,O
228,https://t.co/fDTxm4iXys,O
229,To,O
229,the,O
229,strongest,O
229,!,O
229,#history,O
229,#memes,O
229,https://t.co/NiGVyHnCC9,O
230,Rocking,O
230,my,O
230,Saturday,O
230,night,O
230,in,O
230,the,O
230,bath,O
230,with,O
230,You\'re,O
230,Dead,O
230,To,O
230,Me,O
230,.,O
231,If,O
231,you,O
231,don\'t,O
231,know,O
231,it,O
231,",",O
231,you,O
231,should,O
231,!,O
232,This,O
232,ep,O
232,on,O
232,the,O
232,#history,O
232,of,O
232,fandom,O
232,is,O
232,fascinating,O
232,and,O
232,ace,O
232,.,O
233,They\'re,O
233,all,O
233,ace,O
233,.,O
234,I\'m,O
234,fangirling,O
234,on,O
234,Dr,B-PER
234,Corin,I-PER
234,Throsby,I-PER
234,!,O
234,@BBCSounds,B-ORG
234,@greg_jenner,B-PER
234,@StuGoldsmith,B-PER
234,#hove,O
234,https://t.co/uHmP1eB8G9,O
235,Armenians,B-GPE
235,in,O
235,the,O
235,Byzantine,B-GPE
235,Empire,I-GPE
235,.,O
236,Historians,B-PER
236,consider,O
236,the,O
236,#Armenians,B-GPE
236,to,O
236,have,O
236,been,O
236,one,O
236,of,O
236,the,O
236,most,O
236,influential,O
236,groups,O
236,in,O
236,the,O
236,multi-national,O
236,Byzantine,B-GPE
236,Empire,I-GPE
236,.,O
237,#Armenia'ns,B-GPE
237,engaged,O
237,in,O
237,trade,O
237,",",O
237,administration,O
237,and,O
237,farming,O
237,and,O
237,they,O
237,were,O
237,a,O
237,dominant,O
237,element,O
237,in,O
237,the,O
237,army,B-ORG
237,.,O
237,1/,O
237,#History,O
237,\xf0\x9f\xa7\xb5,O
237,https://t.co/MltwYNfvRU,O
238,Need,O
238,Someone,O
238,to,O
238,ace,O
238,your,O
238,assignments,O
238,?,O
239,#Fall,O
239,Online,O
239,Classes,O
239,#Maths,O
239,#Accounting,O
239,#Stats,O
239,#English,O
239,#Essays,O
239,#Thesis,O
239,#Business,O
239,#Economics,O
239,#Calculus,O
239,#Psychology,O
239,#Philosophy,O
239,#History,O
239,#Assignment,O
239,#Physics,O
239,#Biology,O
239,#Homework,O
239,#Physiology,O
239,#Chemistry,O
239,#Geology,O
239,#Lab,O
239,reports,O
239,Dm,O
239,me,O
239,24/7,O
240,#Do,O
240,my,O
240,homework,O
240,#Online,O
240,class,O
240,#Assignment,O
240,due,O
240,#History,O
240,#javascript,O
241,[],O
241,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6(even,O
241,in,O
241,the,O
241,field,O
241,of,O
241,psychology,O
241,",",O
241,where,O
241,humanistic,O
241,psychology,O
241,was,O
241,shunned),O
241,",",O
241,medical,O
241,professionals,O
241,",",O
241,lawyers,B-PER
241,",",O
241,&amp,O
241,;,O
241,the,O
241,like.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
241,[],O
241,READ,O
241,&amp,O
241,;/or,O
241,dwnld,O
241,entire,O
241,BOOK,O
241,free,O
241,AT,O
241,SITE..,O
241,.,O
242,https://t.co/N5aLZ2YaF4,O
242,#Midterms,O
242,#generations,O
242,#resist,O
242,#culture,O
242,#rebirth,O
242,#psychology,O
242,#history,O
242,CW22,O
242,44849,O
243,Location,O
243,and,O
243,depths,O
243,of,O
243,the,O
243,artesian,O
243,wells,O
243,of,O
243,the,O
243,Black,B-LOC
243,and,I-LOC
243,Grand,I-LOC
243,Prairies,I-LOC
243,of,O
243,Texas,B-GPE
243,1898,O
243,#history,O
243,#map,O
243,https://t.co/4X4u7NsRhu,O
244,#Do,O
244,my,O
244,homework,O
244,#Online,O
244,class,O
244,#Assignment,O
244,due,O
244,#History,O
244,#javascript,O
244,#calculus,O
244,....,O
244,.,O
245,#Dissertations,O
245,Order,O
245,here&gt,O
245,;&gt,O
245,;&gt,O
245,;,O
245,https://t.co/KTstIYR7AH,O
246,#Do,O
246,my,O
246,homework,O
246,#Online,O
246,class,O
246,#Assignment,O
246,due,O
246,#History,O
246,#javascript,O
246,#calculus,O
246,....,O
246,.,O
246,#Dissertations,O
247,Robert,B-PER
247,III,I-PER
247,was,I-PER
247,the,I-PER
247,Count,I-PER
247,of,I-PER
247,Nevers,I-PER
247,from,O
247,1273,O
247,until,O
247,his,B-PER
247,death,O
247,OTD,O
247,in,O
247,1322,O
247,;,O
247,he,B-PER
247,also,O
247,became,O
247,Count,B-PER
247,of,I-PER
247,Flanders,I-PER
247,in,O
247,1305,O
247,https://t.co/G5E4Tc84g4,O
247,#travel,O
247,#France,B-GPE
247,#history,O
248,Boycotting,O
248,History,O
248,won\xe2\x80\x99t,O
248,Change,O
248,it,O
248,.,O
249,#WomanKingMovie,O
249,#WomanKing,O
249,#ViolaDavis,B-PER
249,#African,B-GPE
249,#Dahomey,O
249,#Amazons,O
249,#History,O
249,#Black,O
249,https://t.co/cPChhw4GNa,O
250,Political,O
250,Cartoon,O
250,.,O
251,The,O
251,Soviet,B-ORG
251,Red,I-ORG
251,Army,I-ORG
251,invaded,O
251,Poland,B-GPE
251,#TDIH,O
251,in,O
251,1939,O
251,two,O
251,weeks,O
251,after,O
251,the,O
251,German,B-ORG
251,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
251,launched,O
251,war,O
251,in,O
251,Europe,B-LOC
251,.,O
252,The,O
252,Soviets,B-GPE
252,soon,O
252,occupied,O
252,and,O
252,annexed,O
252,the,O
252,territory,O
252,provided,O
252,by,O
252,the,O
252,Molotov-Ribbentrop,O
252,Pact,O
252,.,O
253,Louisville,B-ORG
253,Courier,I-ORG
253,Journal,I-ORG
253,",",O
253,September,O
253,19,O
253,",",O
253,1939,O
253,.,O
253,#history,O
253,https://t.co/Lwpo7yFtBZ,O
254,September,O
254,17,O
254,-,O
254,81,O
254,WW2,O
254,-,O
254,Allied,O
254,paratroops,O
254,landed,O
254,behind,O
254,German,B-GPE
254,lines,O
254,in,O
254,the,O
254,Netherlands,B-GPE
254,~,O
254,Operation,O
254,Market,O
254,Garden,O
254,.,O
254,#history,O
255,Final,O
255,year,O
255,project,O
255,.,O
256,Displaying,O
256,on,O
256,20th,O
256,September,O
256,at,O
256,University,B-FAC
256,of,I-FAC
256,Gujrat,I-FAC
256,.,O
257,Topic:,O
257,Historical,O
257,sites,O
257,of,O
257,Wazirabad,B-GPE
257,To,O
257,promote,O
257,cultural,O
257,places,O
257,.,O
258,To,O
258,promote,O
258,tourism,O
258,.,O
259,And,O
259,to,O
259,save,O
259,historical,O
259,sites,O
259,.,O
259,#tourism,O
259,#History,O
259,#Punjab,O
259,https://t.co/38NpATolNh,O
260,I,O
260,can,O
260,handle,O
260,your,O
260,due,O
260,essay,O
260,at,O
260,Fair,O
260,price,O
260,.,O
261,#pay,O
261,homework,O
261,#pay,O
261,assignments,O
261,#pay,O
261,hw,O
261,#pay,O
261,maths,O
261,#pay,O
261,chem,O
261,#biology,O
261,#mymathlab,O
261,#nursing,O
261,#lab,O
261,report,O
261,#economics,O
261,#history,O
261,#sociology,O
261,#anatomy,O
261,#research,O
261,#Eassy,O
261,pay,O
261,#Eassy,O
261,DM,O
261,now,O
261,https://t.co/4aMJ8tWxED,O
262,The,O
262,middle,O
262,class,O
262,stagnated,O
262,.,O
263,Repeated,O
263,financial,O
263,crises,O
263,pushed,O
263,people,O
263,into,O
263,the,O
263,arms,O
263,of,O
263,strongmen,O
263,",",O
263,selling,O
263,cliches,O
263,.,O
264,The,O
264,Democrats,O
264,became,O
264,a,O
264,party,O
264,of,O
264,geriatrics,O
264,",",O
264,selling,O
264,endless,O
264,bipartisanship,O
264,.,O
265,All,O
265,that,O
265,mattered,O
265,to,O
265,them,O
265,was,O
265,donor,O
265,money,O
265,.,O
266,Enter,O
266,fascism..,O
266,.,O
267,44623,O
267,#history,O
267,#gerontocracy,O
268,Benjamin,B-PER
268,Barber,I-PER
268,elaborated,O
268,in,O
268,his,B-PER
268,book,O
268,McWorld,O
268,vs,O
268,Jihad,O
268,about,O
268,the,O
268,conflict,O
268,between,O
268,globalization,O
268,and,O
268,tribalism,O
268,in,O
268,a,O
268,post-cold,O
268,war,O
268,world,O
268,.,O
269,The,O
269,West\'s,O
269,labor-capital,O
269,agreement,O
269,ended,O
269,and,O
269,crony-capitalism,O
269,became,O
269,normative,O
269,.,O
270,Inequality,O
270,flourished,O
270,.,O
271,44563,O
271,#history,O
271,#trade,O
271,#China,B-GPE
271,https://t.co/nwGsvy2LuT,O
272,Use,O
272,@eVisitorGuide's,B-PER
272,#Museum,B-FAC
272,Directory,O
272,to,O
272,discover,O
272,#Chicago's,B-GPE
272,world-class,O
272,#museums,B-FAC
272,!,O
273,Discover,O
273,#art,O
273,",",O
273,#dinosaurs,O
273,",",O
273,#science,O
273,",",O
273,#history,O
273,",",O
273,#space,O
273,",",O
273,underwater,O
273,life,O
273,&amp,O
273,;,O
273,much,O
273,more,O
273,!,O
274,https://t.co/Io5JPPlSfV,O
274,#travel,O
274,#budgettravel,O
274,#sightseeing,O
274,#familyfriendly,O
274,#explore,O
274,#fun,O
274,#learn,O
274,https://t.co/EFAiyyjzmV,O
275,Shhh,O
275,\xf0\x9f\xa4\xab,O
275,Do,O
275,not,O
275,tell,O
275,.,O
276,#i\xc3\xa0xiv,O
276,#lifeinmycourt,O
276,#versailles,B-GPE
276,#history,O
276,#louisxiv,B-PER
276,#philippeducdorleans,O
276,#Monsieur,O
276,#chevalierdelorraine,O
276,#Bontemps,O
276,(S4,O
276,e103),O
276,https://t.co/Euc1GoWe5m,O
277,I\xe2\x80\x99m,O
277,knocking,O
277,on,O
277,history\xe2\x80\x99s,O
277,door,O
277,!,O
278,They\xe2\x80\x99ve,O
278,answered,O
278,before,O
278,!,O
279,Will,O
279,they,O
279,answer,O
279,tonight,O
279,?,O
280,Knock,O
280,knock,O
280,\xe2\x9c\x8a\xf0\x9f\x8f\xbe,O
280,\xe2\x9c\x8a\xf0\x9f\x8f\xbe,O
280,#Knocking,O
280,#History,O
280,#Door,O
280,#KennyKalypso,B-PER
280,#Kenny,B-PER
280,#Kalypso,I-PER
280,#DominationZoneWrestling,O
280,#DZW,O
280,#FollowYourDreams,O
280,#MainEvent,O
280,#SupportIndieWrestling,O
280,#IndieWrestling,B-ORG
280,#TexasWrestling,B-ORG
280,https://t.co/NOE2uu09oB,O
281,Political,O
281,Cartoon,O
281,.,O
282,The,O
282,Soviet,B-ORG
282,Red,I-ORG
282,Army,I-ORG
282,invaded,O
282,Poland,B-GPE
282,#TDIH,O
282,in,O
282,1939,O
282,two,O
282,weeks,O
282,after,O
282,the,O
282,German,B-ORG
282,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
282,launched,O
282,war,O
282,in,O
282,Europe,B-LOC
282,.,O
283,The,O
283,Soviets,B-GPE
283,encountered,O
283,minimal,O
283,resistance,O
283,as,O
283,the,O
283,Polish,B-GPE
283,military,B-ORG
283,had,O
283,anticipated,O
283,Soviet,B-GPE
283,neutrality,O
283,.,O
284,Harrisburg,B-ORG
284,Telegraph,I-ORG
284,",",O
284,September,O
284,27,O
284,",",O
284,1939,O
284,.,O
285,#history,O
285,https://t.co/pAH7DsYhsS,O
286,#AmericaFacts,O
286,-,O
286,Our,O
286,first,O
286,monster,O
286,in,O
286,chief,O
286,",",O
286,George,B-PER
286,Washington,I-PER
286,",",O
286,didn\xe2\x80\x99t,O
286,have,O
286,wooden,O
286,teeth,O
286,.,O
287,They,O
287,were,O
287,taken,O
287,from,O
287,slaves,B-PER
287,.,O
288,Maybe,O
288,we,O
288,shouldn\xe2\x80\x99t,O
288,deify,O
288,our,O
288,founding,O
288,sycophants,O
288,so,O
288,much,O
288,.,O
289,#America,B-GPE
289,#History,O
289,#FoundingFathers,B-PER
289,https://t.co/CwpFxWpkET,O
290,Fifteen-year-old,O
290,Rosa,B-PER
290,doesn't,O
290,see,O
290,dead,O
290,people..,O
290,.,O
291,She,O
291,hears,O
291,them,O
291,&amp,O
291,;,O
291,talks,O
291,to,O
291,them,O
291,.,O
292,'5\xe2\xad\x90\xef\xb8\x8fPrepare,O
292,For,O
292,a,O
292,Phenomenal,O
292,Adventure,O
292,(by,O
292,@CCarpinello),B-PER
292,!',O
293,https://t.co/CMK6D8S5Dr,O
293,#youngadult,O
293,#YA,O
293,#history,O
293,#fiction,O
293,#historicalfiction,O
293,#tales,O
293,#legends,O
293,#myths,O
293,#Kindle,O
293,#books,O
293,#ebooks,O
293,#ASMSG,B-ORG
293,#IARTG,O
294,Emperor,B-PER
294,Uda,I-PER
294,",",I-PER
294,59th,I-PER
294,Emperor,I-PER
294,of,I-PER
294,#Japan,I-PER
294,",",O
294,ascended,O
294,to,O
294,the,O
294,Chrysanthemum,B-LOC
294,Throne,I-LOC
294,OTD,O
294,in,O
294,887,O
294,https://t.co/sH4lzHyMeb,O
294,#travel,O
294,#history,O
295,handle,O
295,all,O
295,your,O
295,pay,O
295,#summerclasses,O
295,#Essay,O
295,#Online,O
295,Classes,O
295,#Course,O
295,work,O
295,#Project,O
295,#Essay,O
295,due,O
295,#Pay,O
295,write,O
295,#econometrics,O
295,#Paperpay,O
295,#Someone,O
295,help,O
295,#Case,O
295,study,O
295,#javascript,O
295,#History,O
295,#Homework,O
296,Do,O
296,you,O
296,need,O
296,an,O
296,expert,O
296,to,O
296,handle,O
296,all,O
296,of,O
296,your,O
296,assignments,O
296,?,O
297,DM,O
297,#Research,O
297,papers,O
297,#maths,O
297,#Essay,O
297,due,O
297,#Pay,O
297,write,O
297,#English,O
297,#paper,O
297,pay,O
297,#stats,O
297,#hw,O
297,#Do,O
297,my,O
297,homework,O
297,#Online,O
297,class,O
297,#Assignment,O
297,due,O
297,#History,O
297,#javascript,O
297,#calculus,O
297,....,O
297,.,O
297,#Dissertations,O
298,Do,O
298,you,O
298,need,O
298,an,O
298,expert,O
298,to,O
298,handle,O
298,all,O
298,of,O
298,your,O
298,assignments,O
298,?,O
299,DM,O
299,#Research,O
299,papers,O
299,#maths,O
299,#Essay,O
299,due,O
299,#Pay,O
299,write,O
299,#English,O
299,#paper,O
299,pay,O
299,#stats,O
299,#hw,O
299,#Do,O
299,my,O
299,homework,O
299,#Online,O
299,class,O
299,#Assignment,O
299,due,O
299,#History,O
299,#javascript,O
299,#calculus,O
299,....,O
299,.,O
299,#Dissertations,O
299,https://t.co/rAV76yYOqY,O
300,Quality,O
300,work,O
300,assured,O
300,.,O
301,Dm,O
301,for:-,O
301,#Thesis,O
301,#Coursework,O
301,#Online,O
301,#Assignments,O
301,#Essays,O
301,#Reflection,O
301,papers,O
301,#Essay,O
301,due,O
301,#Pay,O
301,write,O
301,#Do,O
301,my,O
301,homework,O
301,#Pay,O
301,essay,O
301,#Pay,O
301,homework,O
301,#Science,O
301,#Exams,O
301,#Research,O
301,#Pay,O
301,someone,O
301,write,O
301,#English,O
301,#History,O
301,#philosophy,O
301,#Programming,O
301,Hit,O
301,our,O
301,Bio,O
301,for,O
301,More,O
301,info:),O
301,https://t.co/NMgIB5EnpU,O
302,High,O
302,Speed,O
302,Launch,O
302,102,O
302,",",O
302,Motor,O
302,Gun,O
302,Boat,O
302,81,O
302,&amp,O
302,;,O
302,F8,O
302,land,O
302,craft,O
302,trips,O
302,today,O
302,in,O
302,Southampton,O
302,Boat,O
302,Show,O
302,.,O
303,Perfect,O
303,weather,O
303,",",O
303,great,O
303,to,O
303,see,O
303,these,O
303,attracting,O
303,so,O
303,much,O
303,interest,O
303,.,O
304,#WW2,O
304,#History,O
304,#RoyalNavy,B-ORG
304,#RAF,O
304,https://t.co/hzRbJ9JpxP,O
305,Work,O
305,without,O
305,play,O
305,makes,O
305,Jack,B-PER
305,A,O
305,dull,O
305,boy,O
305,.,O
306,Order,O
306,Here&gt,O
306,;&gt,O
306,;&gt,O
306,;,O
306,https://t.co/0bMvU5xtvq,O
306,#assignmenthelp,O
306,#quiz,O
306,#Payessay,O
306,#Physics,O
306,#Essayhelp,O
306,#English,O
306,#essaypay,O
306,#Essayhelp,O
306,#English,O
306,#essaypay,O
306,#Essaydue,O
306,#History,O
307,@BestLawRobert1,B-PER
307,@MUFCUnitedKits,B-ORG
307,@retro_manutd,B-PER
307,@ManUtd,B-PER
307,Yes,O
307,Robert,B-PER
307,the,O
307,five,O
307,made,O
307,their,O
307,contributions,O
307,to,O
307,@ManUtd,B-PER
307,history,O
307,at,O
307,different,O
307,times,O
307,as,O
307,you,O
307,say,O
307,.,O
307,#ManUtd,B-PER
307,#History,O
308,HELLO,O
308,GUYS,O
308,DID,O
308,U,O
308,KNOW,O
308,FLAG,O
308,OF,O
308,NIGGERIA,O
308,?,O
308,!,O
309,MY,O
309,MOM,B-PER
309,SAID,O
309,IT,O
309,TO,O
309,ME,O
309,TRY,O
309,TO,O
309,GUESS...................,O
309,.,O
310,DID,O
310,U,O
310,GUESSED,O
310,?,O
311,ITS,O
311,\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xb1,O
311,#niggeria,O
311,#lgbtfromtoday,O
311,#History,O
311,#FYP,O
312,Congress,B-ORG
312,is,O
312,studying,O
312,whether,O
312,to,O
312,add,O
312,lynching,O
312,sites,O
312,to,O
312,the,O
312,National,B-ORG
312,Parks,I-ORG
312,system,I-ORG
312,to,O
312,help,O
312,more,O
312,Americans,B-GPE
312,remember,O
312,part,O
312,of,O
312,the,O
312,nation\xe2\x80\x99s,O
312,#history,O
312,.,O
312,From,O
312,@statesnewsroom:,B-PER
312,https://t.co/nGgQL2i7Ay,O
313,That\xe2\x80\x99s,O
313,how,O
313,you,O
313,break,O
313,in,O
313,a,O
313,new,O
313,scoreboard,O
313,!,O
314,Great,O
314,#TEAM,O
314,win,O
314,",",O
314,for,O
314,the,O
314,first,O
314,time,O
314,on,O
314,campus,O
314,!,O
314,#History,O
314,#STUFB,O
314,#RaiseTheStandard,O
314,#ShutOut,O
314,https://t.co/yHDXLuO0yu,O
315,Send,O
315,us,O
315,your,O
315,assignment,O
315,prompt,O
315,and,O
315,we,O
315,will,O
315,gladly,O
315,assist,O
315,you,O
315,.,O
316,#essaypay,O
316,#Assignmenthelp,O
316,#Essaydue,O
316,#Onlineclass,O
316,#essaywrite,O
316,#History,O
316,#Paysomeone,O
316,#python,O
316,#Math,O
316,#javascript,O
316,#homework,O
316,#homework,O
316,#Casestudy,O
316,#USA,B-GPE
316,#UK,B-GPE
316,#UAE,B-GPE
316,#Australia,B-GPE
316,#SaudiArabia,B-GPE
316,#Paperpay,O
316,#chemistry,O
316,https://t.co/v1kchml87O,O
317,17,O
317,Sep,O
317,1781,O
317,Chesapeake,B-LOC
317,Bay,I-LOC
317,",",O
317,VA,B-GPE
317,Gen,B-PER
317,George,I-PER
317,Washington,I-PER
317,",",O
317,along,O
317,with,O
317,Gen,B-PER
317,Henry,I-PER
317,Knox,I-PER
317,&amp,O
317,;,O
317,Louis,B-PER
317,Duportal,I-PER
317,",",O
317,confers,O
317,with,O
317,Adm,B-PER
317,comte,I-PER
317,de,I-PER
317,Grasse,I-PER
317,aboard,O
317,his,B-PER
317,110-gun,O
317,flagship,O
317,",",O
317,Ville,O
317,de,O
317,Paris,O
317,.,O
318,Final,O
318,plans,O
318,for,O
318,use,O
318,of,O
318,artillery,O
318,in,O
318,a,O
318,deliberate,O
318,siege,O
318,of,O
318,Yorktown,B-GPE
318,are,O
318,made,O
318,.,O
318,#RevWar,O
318,#History,O
318,#AmRev,O
318,https://t.co/gFeJgIRu6S,O
319,Earl,B-PER
319,Van,I-PER
319,Dorn,I-PER
319,",",O
319,born,O
319,OTD,O
319,in,O
319,1820,O
319,",",O
319,left,O
319,the,O
319,US,B-ORG
319,Army,I-ORG
319,for,O
319,the,O
319,pro-slavery,O
319,Confederacy,B-GPE
319,;,O
319,he,B-PER
319,was,O
319,defeated,O
319,by,O
319,a,O
319,smaller,O
319,Union,B-GPE
319,force,O
319,after,O
319,abandoning,O
319,supply,O
319,wagons,O
319,",",O
319,stranding,O
319,his,B-PER
319,men,O
319,in,O
319,cold,O
319,weather,O
319,https://t.co/tAfVshKzlt,O
319,#CivilWar,O
319,#history,O
319,#BLM,B-ORG
320,[],O
320,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6&amp,O
320,;,O
320,a,O
320,return,O
320,in,O
320,society,O
320,to,O
320,the,O
320,ideals,O
320,&amp,O
320,;,O
320,visions,O
320,of,O
320,a,O
320,better,O
320,world,O
320,that,O
320,had,O
320,so,O
320,inspired,O
320,them,O
320,in,O
320,their,O
320,earlier,O
320,years.\xe2\x80\x9d,O
320,[],O
320,READ,O
320,&amp,O
320,;/or,O
320,dwl,O
320,entire,O
320,BOOK,O
320,free,O
320,AT,O
320,SITE..,O
320,.,O
321,https://t.co/N5aLZ2YaF4,O
321,#Midterms,O
321,#generations,O
321,#resist,O
321,#culture,O
321,#rebirth,O
321,#psychology,O
321,#history,O
321,#WWIIGen,O
321,CW22,O
321,44837,O
322,The,O
322,latest,O
322,A,O
322,Load,O
322,Of,O
322,Babbling,O
322,Nonsense,O
322,!,O
323,https://t.co/XqhC6pQqZw,O
323,Thanks,O
323,to,O
323,@wrathofgod,B-PER
323,@sturdyAlex,B-PER
323,@RichardEGrant,B-PER
323,#aberdeenshire,B-GPE
323,#history,O
324,Political,O
324,Cartoon,O
324,.,O
325,The,O
325,Soviet,B-ORG
325,Red,I-ORG
325,Army,I-ORG
325,invaded,O
325,Poland,B-GPE
325,#TDIH,O
325,in,O
325,1939,O
325,two,O
325,weeks,O
325,after,O
325,the,O
325,German,B-ORG
325,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
325,launched,O
325,war,O
325,in,O
325,Europe,B-LOC
325,.,O
326,While,O
326,denounced,O
326,as,O
326,a,O
326,betrayal,O
326,of,O
326,Poland,B-GPE
326,",",O
326,Britain,B-GPE
326,and,O
326,France,B-GPE
326,avoided,O
326,declaring,O
326,war,O
326,on,O
326,the,O
326,Soviets,B-GPE
326,.,O
327,Washington,B-ORG
327,Evening,I-ORG
327,Star,I-ORG
327,",",O
327,September,O
327,19,O
327,",",O
327,1939,O
327,.,O
327,#history,O
327,https://t.co/kD4mOcrrQv,O
328,Legacy,O
328,of,O
328,Gold,O
328,Leaf,O
328,Craftsmanship,O
328,-,O
328,MIDAS,O
328,TOUCH,O
328,by,O
328,Shehzad,B-PER
328,Khan,I-PER
328,#midastouchbyshehzadkhan,O
328,#shehzadkhan,B-PER
328,#goldleafing,O
328,#gilding,O
328,#goldleaf,O
328,#leafing,O
328,#pinkcityinternational,O
328,#rajasthan,O
328,#jaipur,O
328,#mumbai,B-GPE
328,#india,I-GPE
328,#history,O
328,#origin,O
328,#goldleafgilding,O
328,#art,O
328,#artist,O
328,#crafts\xe2\x80\xa6https://t.co/8B7gD2AUt0,O
329,11/,O
329,The,O
329,Egyptians,B-GPE
329,called,O
329,the,O
329,moment,O
329,of,O
329,creation,O
329,when,O
329,the,O
329,creator,O
329,god,B-PER
329,emerged,O
329,from,O
329,the,O
329,cosmic,O
329,ocean,O
329,the,O
329,zep,O
329,tepy,O
329,meaning,O
329,The,O
329,First,O
329,Event,O
329,.,O
329,#Egypt,B-GPE
329,#History,O
329,#Ancient,O
329,#Egypte,B-GPE
329,#Egipto,B-GPE
329,#Egito,B-GPE
329,#\xce\x91\xce\xaf\xce\xb3\xcf\x85\xcf\x80\xcf\x84\xce\xbf\xcf\x82,O
329,#\xc3\x84gypten,O
329,#\xd7\x9e\xd6\xb4\xd7\xa6\xd6\xb0\xd7\xa8\xd6\xb7\xd7\x99\xd6\xb4\xd7\x9d,O
329,#Egitto,B-GPE
329,#\xe3\x82\xa8\xe3\x82\xb8\xe3\x83\x97\xe3\x83\x88,O
329,#\xec\x9d\xb4\xec\xa7\x91\xed\x8a\xb8,O
329,#\xd0\x95\xd0\xb3\xd0\xb8\xd0\xbf\xd0\xb5\xd1\x82,O
329,#\xd0\x84\xd0\xb3\xd0\xb8\xd0\xbf\xd0\xb5\xd1\x82,O
329,#\xe5\x9f\x83\xe5\x8f\x8a,O
329,#\xe5\x9f\x83\xe5\x8f\x8a,O
329,#\xd9\x85\xd8\xb5\xd8\xb1,O
329,https://t.co/KJkrMq8yZX,O
330,1/,O
330,T-49,O
330,of,O
330,my,O
330,Tutankhamun,B-PER
330,100,O
330,day,O
330,countdown:,O
330,Today,O
330,2,O
330,wooden,O
330,images,O
330,of,O
330,the,O
330,king,B-PER
330,.,O
330,#Egypt,B-GPE
330,#Archaeology,O
330,#history,O
330,#Archaeology,O
330,#Tutankhamen,B-PER
330,#Toutankhamon,B-PER
330,#Tutanc\xc3\xa2mon,O
330,#Tutanchamun,B-PER
330,#\xd8\xaa\xd9\x88\xd8\xaa\xd8\xb9\xd9\x86\xd8\xae\xd8\xa2\xd9\x85\xd9\x88\xd9\x86,O
330,#ancient,O
330,#Tutankam\xc3\xb3n,B-PER
330,#\xe3\x83\x84\xe3\x82\xbf\xe3\x83\xb3\xe3\x82\xab\xe3\x83\xbc\xe3\x83\xa1\xe3\x83\xb3,O
330,#\xe5\x9b\xbe\xe5\x9d\xa6\xe5\x8d\xa1\xe8\x92\x99,O
330,#\xe5\x9c\x96\xe5\x9d\xa6\xe5\x8d\xa1\xe8\x92\x99,O
330,#\xce\xa4\xce\xbf\xcf\x85\xcf\x84\xce\xb1\xce\xb3\xcf\x87\xce\xb1\xce\xbc\xcf\x8e\xce\xbd,O
330,#\xd1\x82\xd1\x83\xd1\x82\xd0\xb0\xd0\xbd\xd1\x85\xd0\xb0\xd0\xbc\xd0\xbe\xd0\xbd,O
330,#\xed\x88\xac\xed\x83\x95\xec\xb9\xb4,O
330,https://t.co/jpYA566p9V,O
331,Political,O
331,Cartoon,O
331,.,O
332,The,O
332,Soviet,B-ORG
332,Red,I-ORG
332,Army,I-ORG
332,invaded,O
332,Poland,B-GPE
332,#OTD,O
332,in,O
332,1939,O
332,two,O
332,weeks,O
332,after,O
332,the,O
332,German,B-ORG
332,Wehrmacht,I-ORG
332,launched,O
332,war,O
332,in,O
332,Europe,B-LOC
332,.,O
333,While,O
333,denounced,O
333,as,O
333,a,O
333,betrayal,O
333,of,O
333,Poland,B-GPE
333,",",O
333,Britain,B-GPE
333,and,O
333,France,B-GPE
333,avoided,O
333,declaring,O
333,war,O
333,on,O
333,the,O
333,Soviets,B-GPE
333,.,O
334,Wilmington,B-ORG
334,Morning,I-ORG
334,News,I-ORG
334,",",O
334,September,O
334,25,O
334,",",O
334,1939,O
334,.,O
334,#history,O
334,https://t.co/2pVu484Il8,O
335,[Quotes/highlights:],O
335,\xe2\x80\x9c\xe2\x80\xa6[the,O
335,60s,O
335,Generation],O
335,were,O
335,biding,O
335,their,O
335,time,O
335,",",O
335,waiting\xe2\x80\x94sometimes,O
335,hopeless,O
335,that,O
335,it,O
335,would,O
335,ever,O
335,arrive\xe2\x80\x94for,O
335,a,O
335,reversing,O
335,of,O
335,the,O
335,pendulum\xe2\x80\xa6\xe2\x80\x9d,O
335,[],O
335,THREAD\xe2\x80\xa6,O
335,https://t.co/nFbKtM8O0Y,O
335,#Midterms,O
335,#generations,O
335,#resist,O
335,#culture,O
335,#rebirth,O
335,#psychology,O
335,#history,O
335,#FBR,O
335,CW22,O
335,44836,O
336,First,O
336,book,O
336,FREE,O
336,.,O
337,Duty,O
337,",",O
337,Honor,O
337,",",O
337,County,O
337,.,O
338,An,O
338,epic,O
338,novel,O
338,of,O
338,West,B-ORG
338,Point,I-ORG
338,and,O
338,the,O
338,Civil,O
338,War,O
338,.,O
338,https://t.co/xqqhd4B8St,O
338,Fans,B-PER
338,of,I-PER
338,the ,I-PER
338,HBO,I-PER
338,miniseries,I-PER
338,Rome,I-PER
338,will,O
338,love,O
338,this,O
338,!\xe2\x80\x9d,O
338,https://t.co/RxxikPK00K,O
338,#history,O
338,#military,O
338,#army,B-ORG
338,#CivilWar,O
338,https://t.co/xqqhd4B8St,O
338,#GoArmy,O
339,We,O
339,all,O
339,forget,O
339,the,O
339,beautiful,O
339,memories,O
339,during,O
339,our,O
339,life,O
339,and,O
339,focus,O
339,on,O
339,our,O
339,regrets,O
339,.,O
340,How,O
340,does,O
340,the,B-PER
340,Catherina,O
340,turn,O
340,her,B-PER
340,regrets,O
340,into,O
340,memories,O
340,?,O
341,Jeannette,B-PER
341,Seibly,I-PER
341,https://t.co/RWCnK9eeIZ,O
341,#familylife,O
341,#Caturday,O
341,#Familysagas,O
341,#HistFic,O
341,#history,O
341,#forgiveness,O
341,#heart,O
341,#MustRead,O
341,#cozy,O
341,#weekends,O
341,https://t.co/zr2kH2gJNn,O
342,Who,O
342,would,O
342,you,O
342,choose,O
342,for,O
342,#Casablanca,O
342,?,O
343,Bogie,B-PER
343,and,O
343,Bergman,B-PER
343,or,O
343,Ronald,B-PER
343,Reagan,I-PER
343,and,O
343,Ann,B-PER
343,Sheridan,I-PER
343,?,O
344,Listen,O
344,to,O
344,the,O
344,history:,O
344,https://t.co/8KNXmRnwly,O
344,#history,O
344,https://t.co/1GcdGMjrSG,O
345,Recommended,O
345,by,O
345,4,O
345,out,O
345,of,O
345,5,O
345,people,O
345,who,O
345,recommend,O
345,things\xe2\x9d\xa3\xef\xb8\x8fLike,O
345,History\xe2\x9d\x93Like,O
345,Random,O
345,Facts\xe2\x9d\x93If,O
345,so,O
345,",",O
345,we,O
345,have,O
345,the,O
345,fact,O
345,for,O
345,you,O
345,",",O
345,check,O
345,out,O
345,today's,O
345,#DailyFactOfTheDay,O
345,and,O
345,let,O
345,us,O
345,know,O
345,what,O
345,you,O
345,think\xe2\x9d\xa3\xef\xb8\x8f#Knowledge,O
345,#OCG,O
345,#Fact,O
345,#Random,O
345,#History,O
345,#OCG,O
345,#consultinglife,O
345,#businesswoman,O
345,#consulting,O
345,#bl,O
345,https://t.co/oBwQKbEt4l,O
346,Bringing,O
346,#Ireland\'s,O
346,#History,O
346,to,O
346,Life,O
346,\xf0\x9f\x87\xae\xf0\x9f\x87\xaa,O
346,\xf0\x9f\xaa\xa1\xf0\x9f\xa7\xa5,O
346,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9c,O
346,My,O
346,colourised,O
346,and,O
346,restored,O
346,c1890s,O
346,Robert,B-PER
346,French,I-PER
346,photo,O
346,of,O
346,Market,B-FAC
346,Street,I-FAC
346,in,O
346,County,B-GPE
346,#Sligo,I-GPE
346,featuring,O
346,a,O
346,Clinchy\'s,O
346,tailoring,O
346,business,O
346,lamppost,O
346,poster,O
346,who,O
346,are,O
346,seeking,O
346,",",O
346,JOURNEYMEN ,B-PER
346,TAILORS,I-PER
346,-,O
346,WANTED,O
346,-,O
346,SEVERAL,O
346,GOOD,O
346,MEN,O
346,\xf0\x9f\x93\x9a#TheColourOfIreland,O
346,https://t.co/yruw5eT8v7,O
347,The,O
347,#seadefenses,O
347,from,O
347,the,O
347,#coldwar,O
347,are,O
347,still,O
347,evident,O
347,along,O
347,the,O
347,coast,O
347,of,O
347,#Tallinn,B-GPE
347,",",I-GPE
347,the,I-GPE
347,#capital,I-GPE
347,of,I-GPE
347,#Estonia,I-GPE
347,.,O
348,#Rusty,O
348,#barbedwire,O
348,corroded,O
348,by,O
348,the,O
348,#sea,O
348,air,O
348,at,O
348,the,O
348,#Patarei,O
348,#SeaFortress,O
348,#macrophotography,O
348,#socialphotography,O
348,#history,O
348,#ThePhotoHour,O
348,",",O
348,see,O
348,more,O
348,at,O
348,https://t.co/VilcfnO0ps,O
348,https://t.co/7STaT2MtqX,O
349,In,O
349,the,O
349,80s,O
349,",",O
349,the,B-LOC
349,Halifax,I-LOC
349,waterfront,I-LOC
349,we,O
349,flock,O
349,to,O
349,today,O
349,was,O
349,still,O
349,a,O
349,big,O
349,",",O
349,vacant,O
349,mess,O
349,",",O
349,says,O
349,Stephen,B-PER
349,Archibald,I-PER
349,",",O
349,and,O
349,he's,O
349,got,O
349,the,O
349,snapshots,O
349,to,O
349,prove,O
349,it,O
349,.,O
350,A,O
350,visit,O
350,to,O
350,the,B-LOC
350,Halifax,I-LOC
350,Seaport,I-LOC
350,and,I-LOC
350,Ocean,I-LOC
350,Terminals,I-LOC
350,c1981:,O
350,https://t.co/jl6OdhjiLr,O
350,#city,B-LOC
350,#history,O
350,#development,O
350,#noticing,O
350,@Cove17,B-PER
350,https://t.co/43Pw7tMoEH,O
351,I,O
351,can,O
351,handle,O
351,your,O
351,due,O
351,essay,O
351,at,O
351,Fair,O
351,price,O
351,.,O
352,#pay,O
352,homework,O
352,#pay,O
352,assignments,O
352,#pay,O
352,hw,O
352,#pay,O
352,maths,O
352,#pay,O
352,chem,O
352,#biology,O
352,#mymathlab,O
352,#nursing,O
352,#lab,O
352,report,O
352,#economics,O
352,#history,O
352,#sociology,O
352,#anatomy,O
352,#research,O
352,#Eassy,O
352,pay,O
352,#Eassy,O
352,.,O
353,#NodeJS,O
353,#IoT,O
353,#Python,O
353,#100DaysOfCode,O
353,DM,O
354,Margaret,B-PER
354,Atwood,I-PER
354,Doesn't,O
354,Think,O
354,We're,O
354,Doomed,O
354,https://t.co/m1CIFj8997,O
354,#hope,O
354,#betterfuture,O
354,#climateaction,O
354,#history,O
354,#drought,O
354,#chaos,O
354,#societyandculture,O
354,#climatefiction,O
354,#youngpeople,O
354,#olderpeople,O
354,#hopeful,O
354,#tools,O
354,#celebrate,O
354,#party,O
354,#howto,O
354,#consequences,O
354,#change,O
355,Trying,O
355,to,O
355,beat,O
355,the,O
355,deadline,O
355,\xf0\x9f\xa4\x94\xf0\x9f\x98\xa5,O
355,Worry,O
355,no,O
355,more,O
355,we,O
355,gat,O
355,you,O
355,covered,O
355,in:,O
355,#onlineclass,O
355,#Pay,O
355,essay,O
355,#Casestudy,O
355,#Desertation,O
355,#Payhomework,O
355,#maths,O
355,#chemistry,O
355,#statistics,O
355,#business,O
355,#Nursing,O
355,#History,O
355,#pay,O
355,assignment,O
355,\xf0\x9f\x93\xa7,O
355,fullclasshelpers@gmail.com,O
355,website:,O
355,https://t.co/V0T3PUVtEz,O
356,Why,O
356,Was,O
356,Western,O
356,Printing,O
356,Superior,O
356,to,O
356,Asian,B-LOC
356,Printing,O
356,?,O
357,Movable,O
357,type,O
357,was,O
357,not,O
357,invented,O
357,by,O
357,Gutenberg,B-PER
357,but,O
357,in,O
357,China,B-GPE
357,and,O
357,later,O
357,advanced,O
357,in,O
357,Korea,B-GPE
357,",",O
357,so,O
357,why,O
357,didn\'t,O
357,Asia,B-LOC
357,have,O
357,a,O
357,printing,O
357,revolution,O
357,?,O
358,Fascinating,O
358,read,O
358,by,O
358,@erikengheim,B-PER
358,#History,O
358,https://t.co/beSdqXEps1,O
359,Hire,O
359,us,O
359,to,O
359,do,O
359,your,O
359,Mathlab,O
359,#Chem,O
359,#English,O
359,#Paper,O
359,pay,O
359,Someone,O
359,help,O
359,paper,O
359,#Case,O
359,study,O
359,#Law,O
359,#essaypay,O
359,Do,O
359,my,O
359,homework,O
359,#Online,O
359,class,O
359,#Religion,O
359,#Chemistry,O
359,#history,O
359,#Econometrics,O
359,#100DaysOfCode,O
359,#NodeJS,O
359,#python,O
359,#WomenWhoCode,O
359,#Nursing,O
359,#Code,O
359,#US,O
359,#Canada,B-GPE
359,https://t.co/vCGYWhlzXM,O
360,I,O
360,have,O
360,a,O
360,#photo,O
360,gallery,O
360,for,O
360,the,O
360,Churches,B-FAC
360,on,O
360,#Gotland,B-LOC
360,in,I-LOC
360,#Sweden,I-LOC
360,at,O
360,https://t.co/g6fLPwakD2,O
360,#medieval,O
360,#History,O
360,#church,B-FAC
360,@GotlandsMuseum,B-ORG
360,@visitsweden,B-PER
360,@visitswedenUK,B-PER
360,@VisitGotland,B-PER
360,@DestGotland,B-PER
360,@regiongotland,B-PER
360,@YesSweden,B-PER
360,@explore_gotland,B-PER
360,@svenskakyrka,B-PER
360,https://t.co/Jq2mDHvL3F,O
361,Is,O
361,the,O
361,Essay,O
361,Urgent,O
361,?,O
362,Order,O
362,Here&gt,O
362,;&gt,O
362,;&gt,O
362,;,O
362,https://t.co/0bMvU5xtvq,O
362,#Essay,O
362,#Researchpaper,O
362,#BuyEssay,O
362,#CustomEssay,O
362,#DoMyPaper,O
362,#WriteMyEssay,O
362,#EssayWritingHelp,O
362,#WriteMyPaper,O
362,#EssayWriter,O
362,#AcademicPapers,O
362,#Essaydue,O
362,#Fallclasses,O
362,#essaypay,O
362,#Essaydue,O
362,#History,O
362,#Assignments,O
362,#Nursing,O
363,#Linux,O
363,kernel,O
363,version,O
363,0.01,O
363,was,O
363,released,O
363,OTD,O
363,in,O
363,1991,O
363,https://t.co/rkcygBzCyn,O
363,#history,O
363,#OpenSource,O
364,Get,O
364,online,O
364,class,O
364,homework,O
364,",",O
364,exam,O
364,help,O
364,#essaypay,O
364,#essaywrite,O
364,essaydue,O
364,#paperpay,O
364,#assignment,O
364,due,O
364,researchpaper,O
364,#accounting,O
364,#finance,O
364,algebra,O
364,#dissertation,O
364,#onlineclass,O
364,PaySomeone,O
364,#paperdue,O
364,#philosophy,O
364,psychology,O
364,#history,O
364,#probability,O
364,#law,O
364,#Assignment,O
364,#USA,B-GPE
364,#Canada,B-GPE
364,#Australia,B-GPE
364,#UK,B-GPE
365,Assignment,O
365,kicking,O
365,your,O
365,ass,O
365,.,O
366,Need,O
366,Help,O
366,?,O
367,order,O
367,here&gt,O
367,;&gt,O
367,;&gt,O
367,;,O
367,https://t.co/0bMvU5xtvq,O
367,#homework,O
367,#thesis,O
367,#quiz,O
367,#Payessay,O
367,#Physics,O
367,#Essayhelp,O
367,#English,O
367,#essaypay,O
367,#Essaydue,O
367,#History,O
367,#Assignments,O
367,#Nursing,O
367,#chemistry,O
367,#essayhelp,O
367,#assignmentslave,O
367,#essaydue,O
367,#onlineclass,O
368,Abba,B-PER
368,Eban,I-PER
368,",",I-PER
368,Israel's,I-PER
368,ambassador,I-PER
368,to,I-PER
368,the,I-PER
368,US,I-PER
368,",",O
368,broadcasted,O
368,this,O
368,offer,O
368,on,O
368,the,O
368,radio,O
368,.,O
369,A,O
369,short,O
369,while,O
369,later,O
369,",",O
369,his,B-PER
369,phone,O
369,rang,O
369,",",O
369,and,O
369,Einstein,B-PER
369,was,O
369,on,O
369,the,O
369,line,O
369,.,O
370,Would,O
370,you,O
370,please,O
370,get,O
370,the,O
370,idea,O
370,out,O
370,of,O
370,Ben-Gurion's,B-PER
370,head,O
370,?,O
371,he,B-PER
371,asked,O
371,.,O
372,It,O
372,was,O
372,absolutely,O
372,out,O
372,of,O
372,the,O
372,question,O
372,.,O
373,#AlbertEinstein,B-PER
373,#History,O
374,After,O
374,the,O
374,death,O
374,of,O
374,Chaim,B-PER
374,Weizmann,I-PER
374,",",I-PER
374,the,I-PER
374,first,I-PER
374,President,I-PER
374,of,I-PER
374,Israel,I-PER
374,.,O
375,Prime,B-PER
375,Minister,I-PER
375,David,I-PER
375,Ben-Gurion,I-PER
375,offered,O
375,the,O
375,presidency,O
375,to,O
375,Albert,B-PER
375,Einstein,I-PER
375,",",O
375,on,O
375,hearing,O
375,the,O
375,offer,O
375,Albert,B-PER
375,Einstein,I-PER
375,was,O
375,dumbfounded,O
375,and,O
375,rejected,O
375,the,O
375,proposal,O
375,.,O
376,#Israel,B-GPE
376,#AlbertEinstein,B-PER
376,#History,O
377,Marie,B-PER
377,Jos\xc3\xa9,I-PER
377,of,I-PER
377,Belgium,I-PER
377,wore,O
377,a,O
377,long,O
377,white,O
377,velvet,O
377,dress,O
377,",",O
377,decorated,O
377,with,O
377,ermine,O
377,fur,O
377,",",O
377,with,O
377,a,O
377,5,O
377,meters,O
377,long,O
377,cloak,O
377,embroidered,O
377,with,O
377,golden,O
377,threads,O
377,and,O
377,a,O
377,lace,O
377,veil,O
377,.,O
378,The,O
378,dress,O
378,was,O
378,designed,O
378,by,O
378,her,B-PER
378,husband,B-PER
378,.,O
379,#royalweddingdress,O
379,#royalwedding,O
379,#weddingdress,O
379,#history,O
379,https://t.co/NRvpm5VO3P,O
380,Political,O
380,Cartoon,O
380,.,O
381,The,B-ORG
381,Soviet,I-ORG
381,Red,I-ORG
381,Army,I-ORG
381,invaded,O
381,Poland,B-GPE
381,#TDIH,O
381,in,O
381,1939,O
381,in,O
381,accordance,O
381,with,O
381,secret,O
381,provisions,O
381,of,O
381,the,O
381,Molotov-Ribbentrop,O
381,Pact,O
381,.,O
382,Premier,B-PER
382,Joseph,I-PER
382,Stalin,I-PER
382,had,O
382,delayed,O
382,the,O
382,invasion,O
382,in,O
382,part,O
382,to,O
382,entrench,O
382,Germany,B-GPE
382,as,O
382,the,O
382,aggressor,O
382,.,O
383,Richmond,B-ORG
383,Times,I-ORG
383,Dispatch,I-ORG
383,",",O
383,August,O
383,23,O
383,",",O
383,1939,O
383,.,O
384,#history,O
384,https://t.co/LM7b022ebZ,O
385,Crazy,O
385,good,O
385,point,O
385,and,O
385,click,O
385,!,O
386,Live,O
386,Tuesdays,O
386,through,O
386,Fridays,O
386,!,O
387,In,O
387,the,O
387,mean,O
387,time,O
387,enjoy,O
387,this,O
387,clip,O
387,!,O
388,https://t.co/98NU8JhR2I,O
388,#fyp,O
388,#foryoupage,O
388,#xyz,O
388,#xyzbca,O
388,#history,O
388,#art,O
388,#gaming,O
388,#videogames,O
388,#twitch,O
388,#contentcreator,O
388,#entertainment,O
388,#discord,O
388,#streamer,O
388,#community,O
388,#TheProcessiontoCalvary,O
388,https://t.co/84nUVYAI33,O
389,17,O
389,Sep,O
389,1779,O
389,Lt,B-PER
389,Col,I-PER
389,Silas,I-PER
389,Talbot,I-PER
389,resigns,O
389,from,O
389,the,B-ORG
389,Continental,I-ORG
389,Army,I-ORG
389,to,O
389,accept,O
389,a,O
389,commission,O
389,as,O
389,a,O
389,Captain,B-PER
389,in,I-PER
389,the,I-PER
389,Continental,I-PER
389,Navy,I-PER
389,.,O
390,The,O
390,only,O
390,officer,B-PER
390,to,O
390,do,O
390,so,O
390,.,O
391,#RevWar,O
391,#History,O
391,#AmRev,O
391,https://t.co/pzmhFNK11p,O
392,PLASTIC,O
392,PANTHER,O
392,?,O
392,!,O
392,!,O
392,!,O
393,VK,O
393,3002,O
393,(M),O
393,Review,O
393,-,O
393,War,O
393,Thunder,O
393,https://t.co/Ltg0EWtYt9,O
393,via,O
393,@YouTube,B-ORG
393,#tank,O
393,#tanks,B-VEH
393,#history,O
393,#game,O
393,#multiplayer,O
393,#military,O
393,#WarThunder_JP,O
393,#WorldofTanks,O
394,Get,O
394,online,O
394,class,O
394,homework,O
394,",",O
394,assignment,O
394,and,O
394,exam,O
394,expert,O
394,help,O
394,with,O
394,#research,O
394,paper,O
394,Essay,O
394,pay,O
394,#Project,O
394,Essay,O
394,due,O
394,#term,O
394,paper,O
394,#econometrics,O
394,#Paperpay,O
394,#Geography,O
394,#,O
394,geometry,O
394,#Matlab,O
394,#History,O
394,.,O
395,Homework,O
395,#Philosophy,O
395,#History,O
395,Thesis,O
395,#Statistics,O
395,Online,O
395,class,O
396,Political,O
396,Cartoon,O
396,.,O
397,The,O
397,Soviet,B-ORG
397,Red,I-ORG
397,Army,I-ORG
397,invaded,O
397,Poland,B-GPE
397,#TDIH,O
397,in,O
397,1939,O
397,in,O
397,accordance,O
397,with,O
397,secret,O
397,provisions,O
397,of,O
397,the,O
397,Molotov-Ribbentrop,O
397,Pact,O
397,.,O
398,The,O
398,agreement,O
398,signed,O
398,in,O
398,August,O
398,1939,O
398,had,O
398,had,O
398,greenlighted,O
398,the,O
398,German,B-GPE
398,invasion,O
398,on,O
398,September,O
398,1,O
398,.,O
399,Richmond,B-ORG
399,Times,I-ORG
399,Dispatch,I-ORG
399,",",O
399,August,O
399,23,O
399,",",O
399,1939,O
399,.,O
400,#history,O
400,https://t.co/Yv8FAhr0hp,O
401,Hoist,O
401,a,O
401,tankard,O
401,in,O
401,memory,O
401,of,O
401,#Conan,B-PER
401,III,I-PER
401,",",I-PER
401,Duke,I-PER
401,of,I-PER
401,Brittany,I-PER
401,",",O
401,who,O
401,died,O
401,on,O
401,this,O
401,day,O
401,in,O
401,1148,O
401,https://t.co/wOSJsOkEJL,O
401,#travel,O
401,#history,O
402,I,O
402,can,O
402,handle,O
402,your,O
402,due,O
402,essay,O
402,at,O
402,Fair,O
402,price,O
402,.,O
403,#pay,O
403,homework,O
403,#pay,O
403,assignments,O
403,#pay,O
403,hw,O
403,#pay,O
403,maths,O
403,#pay,O
403,chem,O
403,#biology,O
403,#mymathlab,O
403,#nursing,O
403,#lab,O
403,report,O
403,#economics,O
403,#history,O
403,#sociology,O
403,#anatomy,O
403,#research,O
403,#Eassy,O
403,pay,O
403,#Eassy,O
403,.,O
404,#NodeJS,O
404,#IoT,O
404,#Python,O
404,#100DaysOfCode,O
404,DM,O
404,@academic334,B-PER
405,@MUFCUnitedKits,B-ORG
405,@retro_manutd,B-PER
405,Great,O
405,photo,O
405,of,O
405,five,O
405,@ManUtd,B-PER
405,personnel,O
405,all,O
405,who,O
405,made,O
405,different,O
405,but,O
405,significant,O
405,contributions,O
405,to,O
405,@ManUtd,B-PER
405,history,O
405,.,O
406,Unusual,O
406,to,O
406,see,O
406,snow,O
406,on,O
406,football,O
406,pitches,O
406,during,O
406,early,O
406,April,O
406,.,O
407,#ManUtd,B-PER
407,#History,O
407,#OldTrafford,O
408,Antietam,B-LOC
408,is,O
408,trending,O
408,.,O
409,It\xe2\x80\x99s,O
409,the,O
409,anniversary,O
409,of,O
409,that,O
409,battle,O
409,in,O
409,the,O
409,civil,O
409,war,O
409,and,O
409,#History,O
409,twitter,O
409,is,O
409,full,O
409,of,O
409,commemorations,O
409,.,O
410,#antietam160,B-LOC
410,(Confession:,O
410,long,O
410,time,O
410,back,O
410,",",O
410,my,O
410,eyes,O
410,saw,O
410,the,O
410,word,O
410,on,O
410,the,O
410,page,O
410,and,O
410,my,O
410,brain,O
410,interpreted,O
410,it,O
410,as,O
410,Dorothy\xe2\x80\x99s,O
410,\xe2\x80\x9cAuntie,O
410,Em\xe2\x80\x9d),O
411,The,O
411,latest,O
411,Revive,O
411,1775,O
411,!,O
412,https://t.co/cQYeTvonjd,O
412,Thanks,O
412,to,O
412,@obriedave1,B-PER
412,@Battlefields,B-PER
412,@Boiarski,B-PER
412,#history,O
412,#otd,O
413,Trying,O
413,to,O
413,beat,O
413,the,O
413,deadline,O
413,\xf0\x9f\xa4\x94\xf0\x9f\x98\xa5,O
413,Worry,O
413,no,O
413,more,O
413,we,O
413,got,O
413,you,O
413,covered,O
413,in:,O
413,#onlineclass,O
413,#Pay,O
413,#javascript,O
413,#Casestudy,O
413,#Desertation,O
413,#homework,O
413,#math,O
413,#chemistry,O
413,#statistics,O
413,#business,O
413,#Nursing,O
413,#History,O
413,#Physics,O
413,#assignment,O
413,Nebraska,O
413,#GoDawgs,O
413,#TOTLEI,O
413,WhatsApp:,O
413,1,O
413,-240,O
413,840-8026,O
414,I,O
414,can,O
414,handle,O
414,your,O
414,due,O
414,essay,O
414,at,O
414,Fair,O
414,price,O
414,.,O
415,#pay,O
415,homework,O
415,#pay,O
415,assignments,O
415,#pay,O
415,hw,O
415,#pay,O
415,maths,O
415,#pay,O
415,chem,O
415,#biology,O
415,#mymathlab,O
415,#nursing,O
415,#lab,O
415,report,O
415,#economics,O
415,#history,O
415,#sociology,O
415,#anatomy,O
415,#research,O
415,#Eassy,O
415,pay,O
415,#Eassy,O
415,.,O
416,#NodeJS,O
416,#IoT,O
416,#Python,O
416,#100DaysOfCode,O
416,DM,O
416,@tutor_100,B-PER
417,Get,O
417,affordable,O
417,tutoring,O
417,and,O
417,essay,O
417,writing,O
417,services,O
417,.,O
418,#Assignment,O
418,.,O
419,#Payessays,O
419,.,O
420,#Calculus,O
420,.,O
421,#Dissertation,O
421,.,O
422,#Finalpaper,O
422,.,O
423,#Exams,O
423,.,O
424,#Quizzes,O
424,.,O
425,#Thesis,O
425,.,O
426,#Powerpoint,O
426,#Statistics,O
426,.,O
427,#Economics,O
427,#Law,O
427,#maths,O
427,.,O
428,#chemistry,O
428,#Homework,O
428,#Algebra,O
428,#Nutrition,O
428,#History,O
428,Lab,O
428,Reports,O
428,Kindly,O
428,DM,O
428,@OlivyaEssays,B-PER
428,https://t.co/4x4pGu5b5L,O
429,Combat,O
429,in,O
429,Fort,B-LOC
429,Frederick,I-LOC
429,https://t.co/hfGPCwiuTb,O
429,#indiegame,O
429,#indiedev,O
429,#indiegames,O
429,#videogames,O
429,#gaming,O
429,#gamedev,O
429,#screenshots,O
429,#screenshot,O
429,#screenshotsaturday,O
429,#pcgaming,O
429,#indiegaming,O
429,#Videogame,O
429,#CivilWar,O
429,#videogaming,O
429,#games,O
429,#History,O
429,#pcgame,O
429,#gaming,O
429,#GamingNews,O
429,https://t.co/rgzC0EJqeC,O
430,Nothing,O
430,ever,O
430,lasts,O
430,forever...#photography,O
430,#Rome,B-GPE
430,#history,O
430,#echoandthebunnymen,O
430,#Italia,B-GPE
430,#design,O
430,#architecture,O
430,#Roma,B-GPE
430,https://t.co/2QENavDHcJ,O
431,Is,O
431,he,B-PER
431,though,O
431,?,O
432,#history,O
432,#memes,O
432,https://t.co/fFV6NoHZnM,O
433,Trying,O
433,to,O
433,beat,O
433,the,O
433,deadline,O
433,\xf0\x9f\xa4\x94\xf0\x9f\x98\xa5,O
433,Worry,O
433,no,O
433,more,O
433,we,O
433,gat,O
433,you,O
433,covered,O
433,in:,O
433,#onlineclass,O
433,#Pay,O
433,essay,O
433,#javascript,O
433,#Casestudy,O
433,#Desertation,O
433,#Payhomework,O
433,#maths,O
433,#chemistry,O
433,#statistics,O
433,#business,O
433,#Nursing,O
433,#History,O
433,#Physics,O
433,#pay,O
433,assignment,O
433,txt:+19793994216,O
433,\xf0\x9f\x93\xa7,O
433,diligent1writers@gmail.com,O
433,https://t.co/FsgtCgeb6F,O
434,Get,O
434,online,O
434,class,O
434,homework,O
434,",",O
434,assignment,O
434,and,O
434,exam,O
434,help,O
434,#Paper,O
434,pay,O
434,#Religion,O
434,#history,O
434,#Econometrics,O
434,#Assignment,O
434,#Chemistry,O
434,#python,O
434,#Math,O
434,#Chem,O
434,Biology,O
434,#Case,O
434,study,O
434,#essaypay,O
434,#marketing,O
434,#Someone,O
434,help,O
434,paper,O
434,#book,O
434,review,O
434,#English,O
434,Essay,O
434,due,O
434,Paper,O
434,write,O
434,#USA,B-GPE
434,#Canada,B-GPE
434,#Australia,B-GPE
434,#UK,B-GPE
435,The,O
435,best,O
435,places,O
435,to,O
435,see,O
435,wonderful,O
435,Roman,O
435,mosaics,O
435,all,O
435,over,O
435,Europe,B-LOC
435,",",O
435,the,O
435,Middle,B-LOC
435,East,I-LOC
435,and,O
435,North,B-LOC
435,Africa,I-LOC
435,.,O
436,https://t.co/DGWYwFBTsx,O
436,#bloggerstribe,O
436,@BloggersHut,B-PER
436,#bloggershutrt,B-PER
436,#theclqrt,O
436,#thebloglist,O
436,#bloggingbeesrt,O
436,#TRJForBloggers,O
436,#allthoseblogs,O
436,@Bloggeration_,B-PER
436,@USBloggerRT,B-PER
436,#History,O
436,#Rome,B-GPE
437,The,O
437,Soviet,B-ORG
437,Red,I-ORG
437,Army,I-ORG
437,invaded,O
437,Poland,B-GPE
437,#TDIH,O
437,in,O
437,1939,O
437,in,O
437,accordance,O
437,with,O
437,the,O
437,Molotov-Ribbentrop,O
437,Pact,O
437,signed,O
437,with,O
437,Nazi,B-GPE
437,Germany,I-GPE
437,.,O
438,With,O
438,Foreign,B-PER
438,Minister,I-PER
438,Vyacheslav,I-PER
438,Molotov,I-PER
438,declaring,O
438,Poland,B-GPE
438,ceased,O
438,to,O
438,exist,O
438,",",O
438,the,O
438,Soviets,B-ORG
438,claimed,O
438,to,O
438,defend,O
438,Ukrainian,B-PER
438,and,I-PER
438,Byelorussian,I-PER
438,blood,I-PER
438,brothers.,I-PER
438,#history,O
438,https://t.co/2AV3FgPlyq,O
439,Enjoying,O
439,Emancipation,O
439,Day,O
439,.,O
440,Honor,O
440,history,O
440,and,O
440,freedom,O
440,.,O
441,#emancipation,O
441,#History,O
441,#freedom,O
441,https://t.co/3Eoo7Dcf4m,O
442,17,O
442,September,O
442,80.7916666666667,O
442,Historical,O
442,Mystery:,O
442,Britain,B-GPE
442,and,O
442,France,B-GPE
442,declared,O
442,war,O
442,on,O
442,Germany,B-GPE
442,over,O
442,her,O
442,invasion,O
442,of,O
442,Poland,B-GPE
442,.,O
443,Why,O
443,didn't,O
443,they,O
443,do,O
443,the,O
443,same,O
443,when,O
443,the,O
443,USSR,B-GPE
443,invaded,O
443,Poland,B-GPE
443,in,O
443,the,O
443,20th,O
443,century's,O
443,biggest,O
443,tag,O
443,team,O
443,event,O
443,?,O
444,#MRP,O
444,#WWII,O
444,#USSR,B-GPE
444,#Poland,B-GPE
444,#Germany,B-GPE
444,#War,O
444,#History,O
444,https://t.co/JlrbPHCiXx,O
445,On,O
445,this,O
445,Day,O
445,in,O
445,1991,O
445,",",O
445,North,B-GPE
445,Korea,I-GPE
445,and,O
445,South,B-GPE
445,Korea,I-GPE
445,were,O
445,admitted,O
445,to,O
445,the,O
445,United,B-GPE
445,Nations,I-GPE
445,.,O
446,#History,O
446,https://t.co/Y3hY8mpHmY,O
447,235,O
447,years,O
447,ago,O
447,today,O
447,",",O
447,our,O
447,Constitution,O
447,was,O
447,ratified,O
447,",",O
447,officially,O
447,making,O
447,it,O
447,the,O
447,law,O
447,of,O
447,the,O
447,land,O
447,.,O
448,#ConstitutionDay,O
448,#Constitution,O
448,#UnitedStates,B-GPE
448,#USA,B-GPE
448,#History,O
448,#Freedom,O
448,#Liberty,O
448,#Rights,O
448,#WeThePeople,O
448,https://t.co/dMIsPXVHu3,O
449,A,O
449,very,O
449,good,O
449,point,O
449,.,O
450,\xf0\x9f\x91\x87,O
450,#PostColdWar,O
450,#history,O
450,#grandstrategy,O
450,https://t.co/Mop6o7z1bM,O
451,English,B-PER
451,architect,I-PER
451,and,I-PER
451,archaeologist,I-PER
451,Charles,I-PER
451,Robert,I-PER
451,Cockerell,I-PER
451,",",O
451,who,O
451,died,O
451,OTD,O
451,in,O
451,1863,O
451,",",O
451,left,O
451,on,O
451,a,O
451,3-year,O
451,Grand,O
451,Tour,O
451,to,O
451,be,O
451,spent,O
451,mostly,O
451,in,O
451,#Greece,B-GPE
451,;,O
451,it,O
451,ended,O
451,up,O
451,lasting,O
451,7,O
451,years,O
451,https://t.co/8G9kqC4ttV,O
451,#travel,O
451,#history,O
452,FreightWaves,O
452,Classics/Leaders:,O
452,Pe\xc3\xb1a,O
452,first,O
452,Hispanic-American,B-PER
452,Secretary,I-PER
452,of,I-PER
452,Transportation,O
452,https://t.co/rvBqtf9sou,O
452,#Museum,B-FAC
452,#History,O
452,#Transport,O
453,#OnThisDay,O
453,in,O
453,#history,O
453,",",O
453,a,O
453,black,B-PER
453,person's,I-PER
453,grandparent,I-PER
453,was,O
453,just,O
453,traded,O
453,.,O
453,https://t.co/nwj5EqY8qz,O
454,Get,O
454,online,O
454,class,O
454,homework,O
454,",",O
454,assignment,O
454,and,O
454,exam,O
454,expert,O
454,help,O
454,with,O
454,Economics,O
454,Finance,O
454,Accounting,O
454,#coursework,O
454,#dissertation,O
454,#Essaypay,O
454,#Onlineclass,O
454,#Homewok,O
454,#History,O
454,#Philosophy,O
454,#economics,O
454,#Statistics,O
454,#Essay,O
454,#homework,O
454,#Assignment,O
454,#maths,O
454,#Calculus,O
454,#USA,B-GPE
454,#Canada,B-GPE
454,#Australia,B-GPE
454,#UK,B-GPE
454,#Germany,B-GPE
455,Things,O
455,would,O
455,have,O
455,been,O
455,a,O
455,lot,O
455,different,O
455,if,O
455,we,O
455,lost,O
455,New,B-GPE
455,Orleans,I-GPE
455,.,O
456,#author,B-PER
456,#jhsanderson,B-PER
456,#draft,O
456,#story,O
456,#howto,O
456,#books,O
456,#writer,B-PER
456,#novel,O
456,#thriller,O
456,#mystery,O
456,#motivation,O
456,#history,O
456,#NewOrleans,B-GPE
456,https://t.co/YNwCKkrbA2,O
457,Get,O
457,online,O
457,class,O
457,homework,O
457,",",O
457,assignment,O
457,and,O
457,exam,O
457,help,O
457,#Math,O
457,Chemistry,O
457,Biology,O
457,#Essaydue,O
457,#English,O
457,#Paper,O
457,pay,O
457,#Case,O
457,study,O
457,#essaypay,O
457,#Onlineclass,O
457,#Religion,O
457,#BookReview,O
457,#Assignment,O
457,#Chemistry,O
457,#physics,O
457,#history,O
457,#Econometrics,O
457,#marketing,O
457,#python,O
457,#USA,B-GPE
457,#Canada,B-GPE
457,#Australia,B-GPE
457,#UK,B-GPE
458,Great,O
458,Day,O
458,Searching,O
458,Today,O
458,\xf0\x9f\x92\xa5,O
458,Check,O
458,out,O
458,Metal,O
458,Detecting,O
458,Uk's,B-GPE
458,video,O
458,!,O
458,#TikTok,O
458,https://t.co/oIuJInrT2u,O
458,#video,O
458,#metaldetecting,O
458,#history,O
458,#norfolkbuttonboy,O
459,Get,O
459,online,O
459,class,O
459,homework,O
459,",",O
459,assignment,O
459,and,O
459,exam,O
459,expert,O
459,help,O
459,#excel,O
459,#Project,O
459,#math,O
459,#Essay,O
459,due,O
459,#Pay,O
459,write,O
459,#English,O
459,#Paper,O
459,pay,O
459,#Case,O
459,study,O
459,#quiz,O
459,#Python,O
459,#Javascript,O
459,#Philosophy,O
459,#book,O
459,review,O
459,#Chemistry,O
459,#physics,O
459,#history,O
459,#geology,O
459,Exam,O
459,help,O
459,#USA,B-GPE
459,#Canada,B-GPE
459,#Australia,B-GPE
459,#UK,B-GPE
459,#Germany,B-GPE
460,https://t.co/C3YZHb7O73,O
460,Any,O
460,#Interesting,O
460,bit,O
460,of,O
460,#History,O
460,.,O
460,.,O
460,.,O
461,in,O
461,regards,O
461,to,O
461,not,O
461,just,O
461,college,O
461,",",O
461,but,O
461,economics,O
461,",",O
461,etc.,O
461,.,O
462,Quality,O
462,work,O
462,assured,O
462,.,O
463,Dm,O
463,for,O
463,#Thesis,O
463,#Coursework,O
463,#Online,O
463,#Assignments,O
463,#Essays,O
463,#Reflection,O
463,papers,O
463,#Essay,O
463,due,O
463,#Pay,O
463,write,O
463,#Do,O
463,my,O
463,homework,O
463,#Pay,O
463,essay,O
463,#Pay,O
463,homework,O
463,#Science,O
463,#Exams,O
463,#Research,O
463,#Pay,O
463,someone,O
463,write,O
463,#English,O
463,#History,O
463,#philosophy,O
463,#javascript,O
463,https://t.co/QHGrjuYTLf,O
464,This,O
464,owl,O
464,was,O
464,carved,O
464,into,O
464,a,O
464,rock,O
464,3,O
464,000,O
464,yrs,O
464,ago,O
464,",",O
464,in,O
464,France,B-GPE
464,.,O
464,#history,O
464,#ancientart,O
464,https://t.co/Z5Ngta1aWF,O
465,Hire,O
465,us,O
465,to,O
465,do,O
465,your,O
465,;,O
465,#Essays,O
465,#Test,O
465,#Anatomy,O
465,#English,O
465,#Programming,O
465,#Exams,O
465,#Political,O
465,science,O
465,#Finance,O
465,#Accounting,O
465,#History,O
465,#Projects,O
465,#Economics,O
465,#Business,O
465,#Statistics,O
465,#Calculus,O
465,#Quizzes,O
465,#Discussions,O
465,#Psychology,O
465,#Computer,O
465,#Theology,O
465,#movie,O
465,review,O
465,#Criminology,O
465,#Excel,O
465,@isabella_expert,B-PER
465,https://t.co/xUXgclzFAF,O
466,EdutainmentDaily,O
466,presenting,O
466,",",O
466,the,O
466,queen,B-PER
466,at,O
466,the,O
466,breaking,O
466,point,O
466,",",O
466,life,O
466,of,O
466,Queen,B-PER
466,Elizabeth,I-PER
466,II,I-PER
466,",",O
466,a,O
466,thread,O
466,(part,O
466,4),O
466,#History,O
466,#QueenElizabethIl,B-PER
466,#QueenElizabeth,B-PER
466,#Queen,B-PER
466,https://t.co/prIFKGQ1Jp,O
467,Kindly,O
467,hmu,O
467,for,O
467,quality,O
467,grades,O
467,.,O
468,#essay,O
468,#homework,O
468,#assignment,O
468,#hw,O
468,#math,O
468,#chem,O
468,#biology,O
468,#onlineclass,O
468,#English,O
468,#mymathlab,O
468,#nursing,O
468,#labreport,O
468,#economics,O
468,#history,O
468,#sociology,O
468,#psychology,O
468,#dissertations,O
468,Dm,O
468,@isabella_expert,B-PER
468,\xf0\x9f\x93\xa7\xf0\x9f\x93\xa7Expertisabella6@gmail.com,O
468,https://t.co/jFiuao7V5q,O
469,PAY,O
469,US,O
469,TO,O
469,HELP,O
469,IN,O
469,YOUR,O
469,DUE,O
469,Homework,O
469,Assignments,O
469,Essay,O
469,Exams,O
469,Online,O
469,classes,O
469,WhatsApp,O
469,+1(551)292-7202,O
469,https://t.co/c2js71V3Nz,O
469,DISCORD,O
469,SERVER,O
469,https://t.co/XXgHJajjyQ,O
469,#History,O
469,#Sociology,O
469,#Philosophy,O
469,#Psychology,O
469,#Astronomy,O
469,#Geology,O
469,#law,O
469,#USA,B-GPE
469,#UAE,B-GPE
469,#Canada,B-GPE
469,#UK,B-GPE
469,#Australia,B-GPE
469,#Kuwait,B-GPE
470,PAY,O
470,US,O
470,TO,O
470,HELP,O
470,IN,O
470,YOUR,O
470,DUE,O
